For -X- _ O
all -X- _ O
recommendations -X- _ O
report -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
click -X- _ O
here -X- _ O
Disclaimer -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
views -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
investment -X- _ O
tips -X- _ O
expressed -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
investment -X- _ O
experts -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
broking -X- _ O
houses -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
rating -X- _ O
agencies -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
moneycontrol.com -X- _ B-ORG
are -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
own -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
website -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
management. -X- _ O
Moneycontrol.com -X- _ B-ORG
advises -X- _ O
users -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
check -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
certified -X- _ O
experts -X- _ O
before -X- _ O
taking -X- _ O
any -X- _ O
investment -X- _ O
decisions. -X- _ O
Cholamandalam -X- _ B-PERSON
Inv -X- _ I-PERSON
and -X- _ I-PERSON
Fin -X- _ I-PERSON
- -X- _ O
24122025 -X- _ O
- -X- _ O
moti -X- _ O

Silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
rose -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
record -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
pushed -X- _ O
higher -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
worsening -X- _ O
geopolitical -X- _ O
tensions -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
expectations -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
Federal -X- _ B-ORG
Reserve -X- _ I-ORG
rate -X- _ O
cuts -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
year. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
white -X- _ O
metal -X- _ O
advanced -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
much -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
0.6 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
67.5519 -X- _ I-MONEY
an -X- _ O
ounce. -X- _ O
Silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
has -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
buoyed -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
speculative -X- _ O
inflows -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
lingering -X- _ O
supply -X- _ O
tightness -X- _ O
after -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
historic -X- _ O
short -X- _ O
squeeze -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
October. -X- _ B-DATE
The -X- _ O
total -X- _ O
trading -X- _ O
volume -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
futures -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Shanghai -X- _ B-GPE
spiked -X- _ O
earlier -X- _ O
this -X- _ O
month -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
levels -X- _ O
near -X- _ O
those -X- _ O
seen -X- _ O
during -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
crunch -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
couple -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
months -X- _ O
ago. -X- _ O
Spot -X- _ O
gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
advanced -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
nearly -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
4,365 -X- _ I-MONEY
an -X- _ O
ounce -X- _ O
– -X- _ O
within -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
20 -X- _ I-MONEY
of -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
all-time -X- _ B-EVENT
high -X- _ I-EVENT
– -X- _ O
having -X- _ O
risen -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
last -X- _ O
two -X- _ O
weeks. -X- _ O
Traders -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
betting -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Fed -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
cut -X- _ O
interest -X- _ O
rates -X- _ O
twice -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
2026 -X- _ B-DATE
after -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
slew -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
economic -X- _ O
data -X- _ O
last -X- _ O
week -X- _ O
did -X- _ O
little -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
provide -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
clarity -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
outlook -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
though -X- _ O
US -X- _ O
President -X- _ O
Donald -X- _ B-PERSON
Trump -X- _ I-PERSON
has -X- _ O
advocated -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
aggressively -X- _ B-EVENT
lowering -X- _ I-EVENT
rates. -X- _ O
Looser -X- _ O
monetary -X- _ O
policy -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
tailwind -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
and -X- _ O
silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
don’t -X- _ O
pay -X- _ O
interest. -X- _ O
Geopolitical -X- _ O
tensions -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
enhanced -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
haven -X- _ O
appeal -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
precious -X- _ O
metals. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
US -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
intensified -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
oil -X- _ B-EVENT
blockade -X- _ I-EVENT
against -X- _ O
Venezuela -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
stepping -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
pressure -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
government -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
President -X- _ O
Nicolás -X- _ B-PERSON
Maduro -X- _ I-PERSON
, -X- _ O
while -X- _ O
Ukraine -X- _ B-GPE
attacked -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
oil -X- _ O
tanker -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
Russia’s -X- _ O
shadow -X- _ O
fleet -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Mediterranean -X- _ B-PERSON
Sea -X- _ I-PERSON
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
first -X- _ O
time. -X- _ O
Precious -X- _ O
metals -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
capping -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
historic -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
and -X- _ O
silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
both -X- _ O
heading -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
strongest -X- _ O
annual -X- _ O
gains -X- _ O
since -X- _ O
1979. -X- _ B-DATE
Silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
has -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
doubled -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
has -X- _ O
surged -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
two-thirds -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
underpinned -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
increased -X- _ O
central-bank -X- _ O
buying -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
inflows -X- _ O
into -X- _ O
bullion-backed -X- _ O
exchange-traded -X- _ O
funds. -X- _ O
Gold-backed -X- _ B-PRODUCT
ETFs -X- _ I-PRODUCT
have -X- _ O
seen -X- _ O
rising -X- _ O
inflows -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
five -X- _ O
straight -X- _ O
weeks -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
according -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
data -X- _ O
compiled -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
Bloomberg -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
World -X- _ B-PERSON
Gold -X- _ I-PERSON
Council -X- _ I-PERSON
figures -X- _ O
show -X- _ O
total -X- _ O
holdings -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
these -X- _ O
funds -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
risen -X- _ O
every -X- _ O
month -X- _ O
this -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
except -X- _ O
May. -X- _ O
Meanwhile -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
has -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
bolstered -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
recent -X- _ O
weeks -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
surging -X- _ O
demand -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
well -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
tightness -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
dislocations -X- _ O
across -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
trading -X- _ O
hubs. -X- _ O
Gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
is -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
rally -X- _ O
further -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Goldman -X- _ B-ORG
Sachs -X- _ I-ORG
Group -X- _ I-ORG
Inc. -X- _ O
analysts -X- _ O
including -X- _ O
Daan -X- _ B-PERSON
Struyven -X- _ I-PERSON
and -X- _ O
Samantha -X- _ B-PERSON
Dart -X- _ I-PERSON
said -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
note -X- _ O
late -X- _ O
last -X- _ O
week -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
setting -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
base -X- _ O
case -X- _ O
scenario -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
4,900 -X- _ I-MONEY
an -X- _ O
ounce -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
risks -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
upside. -X- _ O
ETF -X- _ B-ORG
investors -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
they -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
starting -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
compete -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
central -X- _ B-ORG
banks -X- _ I-ORG
for -X- _ O
limited -X- _ O
bullion. -X- _ O
Silver -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
advanced -X- _ O
0.5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
67.46 -X- _ I-MONEY
as -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
8:27 -X- _ O
a.m. -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Singapore. -X- _ B-GPE
Spot -X- _ O
gold -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
rose -X- _ O
0.5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
4,363.21 -X- _ I-MONEY
an -X- _ O
ounce -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
within -X- _ O
sight -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
record -X- _ O
high -X- _ O
above -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
4,381 -X- _ I-MONEY
in -X- _ O
October. -X- _ B-DATE
Platinum -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
climbed -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
after -X- _ O
jumping -X- _ O
2.5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
on -X- _ O
Friday -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
palladium -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
rose -X- _ O
1.5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
Bloomberg -X- _ B-METRIC
Dollar -X- _ I-METRIC
Spot -X- _ I-METRIC
Index -X- _ I-METRIC
was -X- _ O
little -X- _ O
changed -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Unified -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Payments -X- _ I-PRODUCT
Interface -X- _ I-PRODUCT
( -X- _ O
UPI -X- _ B-TICKER
) -X- _ O
present -X- _ O
itself -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
opportunity -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
merely -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
competition -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
card -X- _ O
network -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
Visa -X- _ B-ORG
Inc. -X- _ I-ORG
CEO -X- _ O
Ryan -X- _ B-PERSON
McInerney -X- _ I-PERSON
said -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
emphasising -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
potential -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
collaboration -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
growth -X- _ B-METRIC
within -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
's -X- _ O
dynamic -X- _ O
fintech -X- _ O
landscape. -X- _ O
In -X- _ O
his -X- _ O
first -X- _ O
trip -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
after -X- _ O
assuming -X- _ O
CEO’s -X- _ O
role -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
November -X- _ O
2022 -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
McInerney -X- _ O
was -X- _ O
blown -X- _ O
away -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
country -X- _ O
's -X- _ O
digital -X- _ O
payment -X- _ O
scene -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
especially -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
UPI -X- _ B-TICKER
, -X- _ O
QR -X- _ B-TICKER
codes -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
soundboxes -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
hailing -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
country’s -X- _ O
digital -X- _ O
payments -X- _ O
innovations -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
transformative -X- _ O
forces. -X- _ O
“What -X- _ O
happened -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
UPI -X- _ B-TICKER
in -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
is -X- _ O
nothing -X- _ O
short -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
remarkable -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
remarked -X- _ O
McInerney. -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
see -X- _ O
it -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
UPI -X- _ B-TICKER
) -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
opportunity -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
Visa -X- _ B-ORG
... -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
help -X- _ O
build -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
financial -X- _ O
inclusion -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
happened -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
result -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
UPI -X- _ B-TICKER
, -X- _ O
work -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
banks -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
create -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
credit -X- _ O
products -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
empower -X- _ O
consumers -X- _ O
financially -X- _ O
helping -X- _ O
them -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
grow -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
credit -X- _ O
ladder -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
build -X- _ O
wealth -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
” -X- _ O
he -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
during -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
fireside -X- _ O
chat -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
News18 -X- _ B-ORG
Rising -X- _ B-EVENT
Bharat -X- _ I-EVENT
Summit -X- _ I-EVENT
2024. -X- _ O
Ryan -X- _ O
's -X- _ O
optimism -X- _ O
extended -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
widespread -X- _ O
adoption -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
QR -X- _ B-TICKER
payments -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
attributing -X- _ O
inspiration -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
local -X- _ O
fintech -X- _ O
innovation. -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
Indian -X- _ O
fintechs -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
opened -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
our -X- _ O
mind -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
power -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
QR -X- _ B-TICKER
payments -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
he -X- _ O
stated. -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
're -X- _ O
looking -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
other -X- _ O
markets -X- _ O
where -X- _ O
QR -X- _ B-TICKER
might -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
form -X- _ O
factor -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
users -X- _ O
prefer -X- _ O
... -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
very -X- _ O
much -X- _ O
came -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
inspiration -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
what -X- _ O
we -X- _ O
've -X- _ O
seen -X- _ O
happen -X- _ O
here -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
India. -X- _ B-GPE
" -X- _ O
In -X- _ O
FY23 -X- _ B-DATE
, -X- _ O
Visa -X- _ B-ORG
network -X- _ O
enabled -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
15 -X- _ I-MONEY
trillion -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
payments -X- _ O
volumes -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
276 -X- _ O
billion -X- _ O
transactions -X- _ O
operating -X- _ O
across -X- _ O
200 -X- _ O
countries. -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
is -X- _ O
among -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
key -X- _ O
strategic -X- _ O
market -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
Visa. -X- _ B-ORG
Outside -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
home -X- _ O
base -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
US -X- _ B-TICKER
, -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
is -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
second -X- _ O
largest -X- _ O
employee -X- _ O
base -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
card -X- _ O
network -X- _ O
giant. -X- _ O
'World -X- _ O
paying -X- _ O
close -X- _ O
attention -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
Stack -X- _ O
' -X- _ O
On -X- _ O
being -X- _ O
asked -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
leveraging -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
stack -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
CEO -X- _ O
remarked -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
world -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
closely -X- _ O
watching -X- _ O
it. -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
There -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
meaningful -X- _ O
opportunity -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
export -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stack. -X- _ O
Aadhaar -X- _ B-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
UPI -X- _ B-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
DigiLocker -X- _ B-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
ONDC -X- _ B-PRODUCT
... -X- _ O
all -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
these -X- _ O
elements -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stack -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
extraordinarily -X- _ O
impressive. -X- _ O
If -X- _ O
you -X- _ O
look -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
product -X- _ O
roadmap -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
transparency -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
I -X- _ O
would -X- _ O
n't -X- _ O
put -X- _ O
it -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
stack -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
against -X- _ O
any -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
best -X- _ O
big -X- _ O
tech -X- _ O
players -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
planet -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
CEO -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

The -X- _ O
small- -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
mid-cap -X- _ O
shares -X- _ O
came -X- _ O
under -X- _ O
sharp -X- _ O
selling -X- _ O
pressure -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Monday -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
investors -X- _ O
booked -X- _ O
profits -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
dragging -X- _ O
several -X- _ O
stocks -X- _ O
down -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
7 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
and -X- _ O
tracking -X- _ O
weakness -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
benchmark -X- _ O
indices. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Smallcap100 -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
index -X- _ O
declined -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
fifth -X- _ O
straight -X- _ O
session -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
slipping -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
2 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
in -X- _ O
intra-day -X- _ O
trade. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
index -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
fallen -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
4 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
over -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
past -X- _ B-EVENT
five -X- _ I-EVENT
sessions. -X- _ I-EVENT
Kaynes -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Technology -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
India -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
was -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
biggest -X- _ O
loser -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Smallcap100 -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
pack. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
dropped -X- _ O
7.36 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
320.5 -X- _ I-MONEY
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
NSE -X- _ B-TICKER
around -X- _ O
1 -X- _ O
p.m. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
counter -X- _ O
extended -X- _ O
losses -X- _ O
after -X- _ O
Kotak -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Institutional -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Equities -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
flagged -X- _ O
concerns -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
inconsistencies -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
company’s -X- _ O
related-party -X- _ O
disclosures. -X- _ O
JP -X- _ B-ORG
Morgan -X- _ I-ORG
advised -X- _ O
investors -X- _ O
against -X- _ O
“bottom -X- _ O
fishing” -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stock. -X- _ O
Data -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Patterns -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
( -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
Reliance -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Power -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
were -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
among -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
drags -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
declining -X- _ O
5.93 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
and -X- _ O
5.25 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
, -X- _ O
respectively. -X- _ O
Other -X- _ O
notable -X- _ O
losers -X- _ O
included -X- _ O
Poonawalla -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Fincorp -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
Aditya -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Birla -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Real -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Estate -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
Anant -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Raj -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
Deepak -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Fertilisers -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
and -X- _ O
Petrochemicals -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Corporation -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
Ola -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Electric -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Mobility -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
fell -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent. -X- _ I-PERCENT
The -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Midcap100 -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
index -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
slipped -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
2 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent. -X- _ I-PERCENT
Godrej -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Properties -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
was -X- _ O
among -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
top -X- _ O
laggards -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
dropping -X- _ O
5.54 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
115.30 -X- _ I-MONEY
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
NSE. -X- _ B-TICKER
Mahindra -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
& -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Mahindra -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Financial -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Services -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
Bharat -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Dynamics -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
Housing -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
& -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Urban -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Development -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Corporation -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
and -X- _ O
Prestige -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
Estates -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Projects -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
were -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
down -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
much -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent. -X- _ I-PERCENT
Broader -X- _ O
market -X- _ O
sentiment -X- _ O
remained -X- _ O
weak -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
mirroring -X- _ O
declines -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Sensex -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
and -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
as -X- _ O
investors -X- _ O
turned -X- _ O
cautious -X- _ O
ahead -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
US -X- _ O
Federal -X- _ B-ORG
Reserve’s -X- _ I-ORG
policy -X- _ B-EVENT
meeting -X- _ I-EVENT
and -X- _ O
continued -X- _ O
foreign -X- _ O
fund -X- _ O
outflows. -X- _ O
At -X- _ O
around -X- _ O
12:30 -X- _ O
p.m. -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Sensex -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
was -X- _ O
down -X- _ O
458.52 -X- _ O
points -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
0.53 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
at -X- _ O
85,253.85. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
slipped -X- _ O
170.80 -X- _ O
points -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
0.65 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
26,015.65 -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

ICICI -X- _ B-TICKER
Prudential -X- _ B-ORG
Asset -X- _ I-ORG
Management -X- _ I-ORG
Company -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
preparing -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
series -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
fund -X- _ O
launches -X- _ O
under -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
newly -X- _ O
created -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
SEBI-approved -X- _ B-ORG
SIF -X- _ B-TICKER
category -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
Managing -X- _ O
Director -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
CEO -X- _ O
Nimesh -X- _ B-PERSON
Shah -X- _ I-PERSON
expressing -X- _ O
optimism -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
long-term -X- _ O
potential -X- _ O
while -X- _ O
emphasising -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
early -X- _ O
traction -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
take -X- _ O
time. -X- _ O
He -X- _ O
was -X- _ O
speaking -X- _ O
during -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
exclusive -X- _ O
interaction -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
Moneycontrol -X- _ B-ORG
at -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
AMC’s -X- _ B-TICKER
bumper -X- _ O
IPO -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
launch. -X- _ B-EVENT
The -X- _ O
issue -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
100 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
OFS -X- _ B-TICKER
of -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
9.91 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
equity -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
capital. -X- _ O
ICICI -X- _ B-TICKER
Prudential -X- _ O
AMC -X- _ B-ORG
is -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
joint -X- _ O
venture -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
ICICI -X- _ B-ORG
Bank -X- _ I-ORG
and -X- _ O
Prudential -X- _ B-ORG
Corporation -X- _ I-ORG
Holdings -X- _ I-ORG
Limited. -X- _ I-ORG
It -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
currently -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
second-largest -X- _ O
AMC -X- _ B-TICKER
by -X- _ O
AUM -X- _ B-PRODUCT
and -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
sixth -X- _ O
AMC -X- _ B-TICKER
to -X- _ O
go -X- _ O
public. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
price -X- _ O
band -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
fixed -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
2,061–2,165 -X- _ I-MONEY
per -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
valuing -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
company -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
around -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
10,600 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
at -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
top -X- _ O
end. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
issue -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
open -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ B-DATE
12 -X- _ I-DATE
and -X- _ O
close -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ B-DATE
16. -X- _ I-DATE
Speaking -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
SIF -X- _ B-TICKER
category -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Shah -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
SEBI -X- _ B-ORG
“has -X- _ O
thought -X- _ O
through -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
SIF -X- _ B-TICKER
category -X- _ O
very -X- _ O
well -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
” -X- _ O
adding -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
segment -X- _ O
holds -X- _ O
significant -X- _ O
long-term -X- _ O
promise. -X- _ O
However -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
he -X- _ O
cautioned -X- _ O
against -X- _ O
expecting -X- _ O
immediate -X- _ O
scale. -X- _ O
“It -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
happen. -X- _ O
I -X- _ O
don’t -X- _ O
expect -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
something -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
happen -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
6 -X- _ O
months -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
1 -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
” -X- _ O
he -X- _ O
noted. -X- _ O
Currently -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
around -X- _ O
four -X- _ O
mutual -X- _ O
funds -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
launched -X- _ O
SIF -X- _ B-TICKER
products -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
including -X- _ O
Edelweiss -X- _ B-ORG
Mutual -X- _ I-ORG
Fund -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
SBI -X- _ B-TICKER
Mutual -X- _ B-ORG
Fund -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
ITI -X- _ B-ORG
AMC -X- _ I-ORG
and -X- _ O
Quant -X- _ B-ORG
AMC -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
among -X- _ O
others. -X- _ O
ICICI -X- _ B-ORG
Prudential -X- _ I-ORG
AMC -X- _ I-ORG
currently -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
13.2 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
market -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
reported -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
profit -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
1,618 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
and -X- _ O
revenue -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
2,949 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
six -X- _ O
months -X- _ O
ended -X- _ O
September -X- _ B-DATE
2025—up -X- _ I-DATE
21.9 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
and -X- _ O
20 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
respectively -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
earlier. -X- _ O
For -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
financial -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
ended -X- _ O
March -X- _ B-DATE
2025 -X- _ I-DATE
, -X- _ O
profit -X- _ O
rose -X- _ O
29.3 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
2,651 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
, -X- _ O
while -X- _ O
revenue -X- _ O
surged -X- _ O
32.4 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
4,977 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore. -X- _ I-MONEY
The -X- _ O
firm -X- _ O
manages -X- _ O
143 -X- _ O
mutual -X- _ B-PRODUCT
fund -X- _ I-PRODUCT
schemes -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
highest -X- _ O
among -X- _ O
domestic -X- _ O
asset -X- _ O
managers. -X- _ O
Other -X- _ O
AMCs -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
listed -X- _ O
space -X- _ O
include -X- _ O
HDFC -X- _ B-TICKER
AMC -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
Nippon -X- _ B-ORG
Life -X- _ I-ORG
India -X- _ I-ORG
Asset -X- _ I-ORG
Management -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
UTI -X- _ B-TICKER
AMC -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
Canara -X- _ B-ORG
Robeco -X- _ I-ORG
AMC -X- _ B-TICKER
and -X- _ O
Aditya -X- _ B-ORG
Birla -X- _ I-ORG
Sun -X- _ I-ORG
Life -X- _ I-ORG
AMC. -X- _ B-TICKER
Follow -X- _ O
all -X- _ O
IPO -X- _ O
news -X- _ O
here -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Christmas -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
United -X- _ B-GPE
States -X- _ I-GPE
may -X- _ O
weigh -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
wallet -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
little -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
this -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
— -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
just -X- _ O
because -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
festive -X- _ O
splurge. -X- _ O
A -X- _ O
Moneycontrol -X- _ B-ORG
analysis -X- _ O
shows -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
three -X- _ O
largest -X- _ O
suppliers -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Christmas -X- _ O
merchandise -X- _ O
account -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
90 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
of -X- _ O
America -X- _ B-ORG
's -X- _ O
festive -X- _ O
imports -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
face -X- _ O
high -X- _ O
tariffs. -X- _ O
From -X- _ O
tree -X- _ B-PRODUCT
ornaments -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
nativity -X- _ B-PRODUCT
figurines -X- _ I-PRODUCT
to -X- _ O
plastic -X- _ B-PRODUCT
decorations -X- _ I-PRODUCT
and -X- _ O
wooden -X- _ B-PRODUCT
collectibles -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
US -X- _ O
' -X- _ O
Christmas -X- _ O
supply -X- _ O
chain -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
overwhelmingly -X- _ O
concentrated -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Asia. -X- _ B-GPE
China -X- _ B-GPE
dominates -X- _ O
most -X- _ O
key -X- _ O
product -X- _ O
lines -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
commanding -X- _ O
85–88 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
of -X- _ O
US -X- _ B-TICKER
imports -X- _ O
across -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
Christmas -X- _ O
categories. -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
while -X- _ O
far -X- _ O
smaller -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
scale -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
remains -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
second-most -X- _ O
important -X- _ O
supplier -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
particularly -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
wooden -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
handcrafted -X- _ O
segments. -X- _ O
China’s -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
lead -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
largest -X- _ O
Christmas -X- _ O
category -X- _ O
— -X- _ O
ornaments -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
made -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
glass -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
wood -X- _ O
— -X- _ O
highlights -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
imbalance. -X- _ O
In -X- _ O
2024 -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
US -X- _ B-TICKER
imported -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
2.55 -X- _ I-MONEY
billion -X- _ I-MONEY
worth -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
these -X- _ O
items -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
China -X- _ B-GPE
accounted -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
2.24 -X- _ I-MONEY
billion -X- _ I-MONEY
, -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
nearly -X- _ O
88 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent. -X- _ I-PERCENT
India -X- _ B-GPE
shipped -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
44.3 -X- _ I-MONEY
million -X- _ I-MONEY
, -X- _ O
ranking -X- _ O
third -X- _ O
after -X- _ O
China -X- _ B-GPE
and -X- _ O
Cambodia -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
exported -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
165 -X- _ I-MONEY
million -X- _ I-MONEY
worth -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
goods. -X- _ O
A -X- _ O
similar -X- _ O
pattern -X- _ O
plays -X- _ O
out -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
plastic -X- _ B-PRODUCT
decorations -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
segment -X- _ O
worth -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
589.7 -X- _ I-MONEY
million. -X- _ I-MONEY
Chinese -X- _ O
goods -X- _ O
accounted -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
$ -X- _ B-MONEY
508 -X- _ I-MONEY
million. -X- _ I-MONEY
Where -X- _ B-PERSON
India -X- _ I-PERSON
stands -X- _ O
out -X- _ O
India’s -X- _ O
strength -X- _ O
lies -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
artisan -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
niche -X- _ O
festive -X- _ O
categories. -X- _ O
In -X- _ O
glass -X- _ B-PRODUCT
ornaments -X- _ I-PRODUCT
and -X- _ O
wooden -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Christmas -X- _ I-PRODUCT
decorations -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
consistently -X- _ O
ranks -X- _ O
among -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
top -X- _ O
three -X- _ O
suppliers -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
reflecting -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
foothold -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
handcrafted -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
higher-value -X- _ O
festive -X- _ O
products -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
cater -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
premium -X- _ O
buyers. -X- _ O
Highly -X- _ O
concentrated -X- _ O
supply -X- _ O
chain -X- _ O
Overall -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
US -X- _ B-TICKER
Christmas -X- _ O
import -X- _ O
market -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
strikingly -X- _ O
concentrated. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
top -X- _ O
five -X- _ O
supplier -X- _ O
countries -X- _ O
account -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
nearly -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
entire -X- _ O
market -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
led -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
China -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
followed -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
Cambodia -X- _ B-GPE
and -X- _ O
India. -X- _ B-GPE
European -X- _ B-PERSON
Union -X- _ I-PERSON
nations -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
select -X- _ O
Southeast -X- _ B-PERSON
Asian -X- _ I-PERSON
exporters -X- _ O
occupy -X- _ O
much -X- _ O
smaller -X- _ O
place. -X- _ O
China’s -X- _ O
dominance -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
confined -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
US. -X- _ B-TICKER
Across -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
global -X- _ O
markets -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
including -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
European -X- _ B-PERSON
Union -X- _ I-PERSON
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
United -X- _ B-PERSON
Kingdom -X- _ I-PERSON
, -X- _ O
Japan -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
Canada -X- _ B-GPE
and -X- _ O
Australia -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
Chinese -X- _ O
festive -X- _ O
products -X- _ O
routinely -X- _ O
command -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
90 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
market -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
several -X- _ O
categories. -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
ranks -X- _ O
third -X- _ O
globally -X- _ O
after -X- _ O
Cambodia -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
accounting -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
1.9 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
of -X- _ O
worldwide -X- _ O
Christmas -X- _ O
merchandise -X- _ O
imports. -X- _ O
In -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
EU -X- _ B-GPE
and -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
UK -X- _ B-GPE
, -X- _ O
however -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
fares -X- _ O
better -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ranking -X- _ O
second -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
2 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
market -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Prabhudas -X- _ B-PERSON
Lilladher -X- _ I-PERSON
's -X- _ O
research -X- _ O
report -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
GE -X- _ B-TICKER
Vernova -X- _ I-TICKER
T -X- _ I-TICKER
& -X- _ I-TICKER
D -X- _ I-TICKER
India -X- _ B-GPE
We -X- _ O
revise -X- _ O
our -X- _ O
FY27 -X- _ B-DATE
/ -X- _ I-DATE
28E -X- _ I-DATE
EPS -X- _ B-TICKER
estimates -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
+14 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
/ -X- _ O
+13 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
and -X- _ O
upgrade -X- _ O
our -X- _ O
rating -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
‘Accumulate’ -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
‘Buy’ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
factoring -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
award -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Khavda-South -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Olpad -X- _ I-PRODUCT
VSC -X- _ I-PRODUCT
HVDC -X- _ I-PRODUCT
project. -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
estimate -X- _ O
this -X- _ O
order -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
drive -X- _ O
incremental -X- _ O
EPS -X- _ B-TICKER
of -X- _ O
~Rs6.8 -X- _ B-MONEY
in -X- _ O
FY27 -X- _ B-DATE
and -X- _ O
~Rs7.8 -X- _ B-MONEY
in -X- _ O
FY28. -X- _ B-DATE
In -X- _ O
our -X- _ O
post-order -X- _ O
win -X- _ O
discussion -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
management -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
they -X- _ O
highlighted -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
robust -X- _ O
~Rs1.0trn+ -X- _ B-MONEY
HVDC -X- _ B-PRODUCT
pipeline -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
awarded -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-GPE
over -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
2-3 -X- _ O
years. -X- _ O
Beyond -X- _ O
HVDC -X- _ B-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
base -X- _ O
orders -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
grow -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
healthy -X- _ O
10-15 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
YoY -X- _ O
including -X- _ O
STATCOMs -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
add -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
~Rs40bn -X- _ B-MONEY
annual -X- _ O
addressable -X- _ O
opportunity -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
medium -X- _ O
term. -X- _ O
Supported -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
focused -X- _ O
~Rs10.6bn -X- _ B-MONEY
capex -X- _ O
program -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
global -X- _ O
parent’s -X- _ O
“Asia -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
Asia” -X- _ O
strategy -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
driving -X- _ O
higher -X- _ O
localization -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
high-value -X- _ O
export -X- _ O
orders -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
~Rs25bn -X- _ B-MONEY
order -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
FY27 -X- _ B-DATE
) -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
we -X- _ O
expect -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
sustained -X- _ O
execution -X- _ O
ramp-up -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
improved -X- _ O
operating -X- _ O
leverage -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
result -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
EBITDA -X- _ B-METRIC
margin -X- _ I-METRIC
sustenance -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
20 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
medium -X- _ O
term. -X- _ O
Outlook -X- _ B-ORG
We -X- _ I-ORG
believe -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
1 -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
GVTD’s -X- _ B-ORG
strong -X- _ O
position -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
HVDC -X- _ B-PRODUCT
with -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
recent -X- _ O
Khavda -X- _ B-PRODUCT
– -X- _ I-PRODUCT
South -X- _ I-PRODUCT
Olpad -X- _ I-PRODUCT
win -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
2 -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
robust -X- _ O
order -X- _ O
book -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
Rs131.1bn -X- _ B-MONEY
) -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
3 -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
management’s -X- _ O
focus -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
margin -X- _ O
improvement -X- _ O
augur -X- _ O
well -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
strong -X- _ O
revenue -X- _ O
& -X- _ O
profit -X- _ O
growth -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
GVTD. -X- _ B-ORG
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
trading -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
P -X- _ B-METRIC
/ -X- _ I-METRIC
E -X- _ I-METRIC
of -X- _ O
56.1x -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
45.5x -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
FY27 -X- _ B-DATE
/ -X- _ O
28E. -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
value -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
PE -X- _ B-METRIC
of -X- _ O
65x -X- _ O
Sep’27E -X- _ B-DATE
( -X- _ O
same -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
earlier -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
arriving -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
TP -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
4,005 -X- _ I-MONEY
( -X- _ O
Rs3,531 -X- _ B-MONEY
earlier -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

The -X- _ O
shares -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
of -X- _ O
Lenskart -X- _ B-ORG
Solutions -X- _ I-ORG
fell -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
3 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ B-DATE
8 -X- _ I-DATE
after -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
one-month -X- _ O
shareholder -X- _ O
lock-in -X- _ O
period -X- _ O
came -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
end. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
shares -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
dropped -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
403.20 -X- _ I-MONEY
apiece -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Monday. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
has -X- _ O
made -X- _ O
only -X- _ O
marginal -X- _ O
gains -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
IPO -X- _ B-EVENT
price -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
first -X- _ O
one -X- _ O
month -X- _ O
since -X- _ O
listing. -X- _ O
Around -X- _ O
4.07 -X- _ O
crore -X- _ O
shares -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
2 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
company -X- _ O
's -X- _ O
stake -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
free -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
trade -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
lock-in -X- _ O
comes -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
an -X- _ O
end -X- _ O
today -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
CNBC-TV18 -X- _ B-ORG
quoted -X- _ O
Nuvama -X- _ B-ORG
Alternative -X- _ I-ORG
& -X- _ I-ORG
Quantitative -X- _ I-ORG
Research -X- _ I-ORG
as -X- _ O
saying. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
number -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
shares -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
will -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
cumulatively -X- _ O
worth -X- _ O
around -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
1,700 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
based -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stock -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
's -X- _ O
previous -X- _ O
closing -X- _ O
price -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
417.20 -X- _ I-MONEY
per -X- _ O
share. -X- _ O
However -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
this -X- _ O
does -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
imply -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
all -X- _ O
these -X- _ O
shares -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
offloaded -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
market -X- _ O
immediately. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
expiry -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
lock-in -X- _ O
period -X- _ O
simply -X- _ O
means -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
these -X- _ O
shares -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
can -X- _ O
now -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
traded. -X- _ O
Lenskart -X- _ O
shares -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
are -X- _ O
currently -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
only -X- _ O
0.3 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
from -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
IPO -X- _ O
price -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
403.2 -X- _ I-MONEY
apiece -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
2 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
from -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
listing -X- _ O
price -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
395 -X- _ I-MONEY
per -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
NSE. -X- _ B-GPE
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
had -X- _ O
listed -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
discount -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
stock -X- _ B-GPE
markets -X- _ I-GPE
on -X- _ O
November -X- _ O
10. -X- _ O
This -X- _ O
came -X- _ O
despite -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
7,278-crore -X- _ I-MONEY
IPO -X- _ B-EVENT
seeing -X- _ O
strong -X- _ O
investor -X- _ O
interest -X- _ O
during -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
three -X- _ O
days -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
public -X- _ O
bidding -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
being -X- _ O
subscribed -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
28 -X- _ O
times -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
offer -X- _ O
size. -X- _ O
After -X- _ O
listing -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stock -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
rose -X- _ O
nearly -X- _ O
14 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
to -X- _ O
hit -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
high -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
448.80 -X- _ I-MONEY
apiece -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ O
1. -X- _ O
However -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
shares -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
popular -X- _ O
eyewear-retailer -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
now -X- _ O
fallen -X- _ O
nearly -X- _ O
10 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
since -X- _ O
then. -X- _ O
Lenskart -X- _ B-ORG
in -X- _ O
November -X- _ O
reported -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
net -X- _ O
profit -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
103.5 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
second -X- _ O
quarter -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
financial -X- _ O
year -X- _ O
2026. -X- _ O
This -X- _ O
marked -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
20 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
year-on-year -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
YoY -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
increase -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
86.3 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
net -X- _ O
profit -X- _ O
reported -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
same -X- _ O
period -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
previous -X- _ O
financial -X- _ O
year. -X- _ O
Its -X- _ O
revenue -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
operations -X- _ O
rose -X- _ O
21 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
YoY -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
2,096 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
in -X- _ O
Q2 -X- _ B-DATE
FY26. -X- _ I-DATE
Follow -X- _ O
all -X- _ O
LIVE -X- _ B-TICKER
updates -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
markets -X- _ O
here -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

PC -X- _ B-ORG
Jeweller -X- _ I-ORG
shares -X- _ O
rose -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Monday -X- _ O
after -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
company -X- _ O
announced -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
collaboration -X- _ O
aimed -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
supporting -X- _ O
goldsmiths -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Uttar -X- _ B-PERSON
Pradesh. -X- _ I-PERSON
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
was -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
nearly -X- _ O
1 -X- _ B-PERCENT
percent -X- _ I-PERCENT
on -X- _ O
Monday -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
trading -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
11.14 -X- _ I-MONEY
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
NSE -X- _ B-ORG
at -X- _ O
around -X- _ O
11 -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
30 -X- _ O
a.m. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
shares -X- _ O
were -X- _ O
seen -X- _ O
2.17 -X- _ B-PERCENT
per -X- _ I-PERCENT
cent -X- _ I-PERCENT
higher -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
11.29 -X- _ I-MONEY
, -X- _ O
it -X- _ O
's -X- _ O
intraday -X- _ O
high. -X- _ O
In -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
statement -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Delhi-based -X- _ O
company -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
it -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
partnered -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
CM -X- _ B-PERSON
Yuva -X- _ I-PERSON
Udyami -X- _ I-PERSON
Yojana -X- _ I-PERSON
to -X- _ O
help -X- _ O
1,000 -X- _ O
PM -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Vishwakarma-certified -X- _ I-PRODUCT
goldsmiths -X- _ I-PRODUCT
( -X- _ O
Sunar -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
first -X- _ O
phase. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
initiative -X- _ O
seeks -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
enable -X- _ O
these -X- _ O
artisans -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
rural -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
semi-urban -X- _ O
parts -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Uttar -X- _ B-PERSON
Pradesh -X- _ I-PERSON
to -X- _ O
become -X- _ O
jewellery -X- _ O
entrepreneurs -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
organised -X- _ O
retail -X- _ O
partners. -X- _ O
PC -X- _ B-ORG
Jeweller -X- _ I-ORG
said -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
tie-up -X- _ O
will -X- _ O
offer -X- _ O
support -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
branding -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
design -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
modern -X- _ O
retail -X- _ O
practices -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
digital -X- _ O
skills -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
market -X- _ O
linkages. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
company -X- _ O
added -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
programme -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
cover -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
5,000 -X- _ O
such -X- _ O
artisans -X- _ O
across -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
country. -X- _ O
According -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
firm -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
85,000 -X- _ O
PM -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Vishwakarma-certified -X- _ I-PRODUCT
goldsmith -X- _ I-PRODUCT
artisans -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
currently -X- _ O
verified -X- _ O
nationwide. -X- _ O
PC -X- _ B-TICKER
Jeweller -X- _ O
operates -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
50 -X- _ O
stores -X- _ O
across -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Defence -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
shares -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
rose -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
fifth -X- _ O
consecutive -X- _ O
session -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ O
26 -X- _ O
amid -X- _ O
geopolitical -X- _ O
tensions -X- _ O
flaring -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
different -X- _ O
parts -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
world -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
year-end -X- _ O
Defence -X- _ B-ORG
Acquisition -X- _ I-ORG
Council -X- _ I-ORG
meeting -X- _ O
today. -X- _ O
Defence -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
Bharat -X- _ B-ORG
Electronics -X- _ I-ORG
traded -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
1 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
higher -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
was -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
best -X- _ O
performing -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
50 -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
stock. -X- _ O
Outside -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
50 -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
, -X- _ O
shares -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Paras -X- _ B-ORG
Defence -X- _ I-ORG
and -X- _ I-ORG
Space -X- _ I-ORG
Technologies -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
Mtar -X- _ B-ORG
Technologies -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
Mazagon -X- _ B-ORG
Dock -X- _ I-ORG
Shipbuilders -X- _ I-ORG
were -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
2–3 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
and -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
India -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Defence -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
index -X- _ O
was -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
1 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
, -X- _ O
higher -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
any -X- _ O
other -X- _ O
sectoral -X- _ O
index. -X- _ O
A -X- _ O
report -X- _ O
said -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
defence -X- _ O
deals -X- _ O
worth -X- _ O
Rs -X- _ B-MONEY
80,000 -X- _ I-MONEY
crore -X- _ I-MONEY
are -X- _ O
likely -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
approved -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
Rajnath -X- _ B-PERSON
Singh-led -X- _ I-PERSON
DAC -X- _ B-TICKER
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ O
26. -X- _ O
Several -X- _ O
defence -X- _ O
deals -X- _ O
may -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
cleared -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
strengthen -X- _ O
air -X- _ O
defence -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
ISR -X- _ B-TICKER
capabilities -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
reported -X- _ O
ET -X- _ B-ORG
NOW. -X- _ I-ORG
Procurement -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Embraer-based -X- _ O
Airborne -X- _ O
Early -X- _ O
Warning -X- _ O
System -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
NETRA -X- _ B-TICKER
AEW -X- _ B-TICKER
integration -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
agenda -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
report -X- _ O
added. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
rise -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
defence -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
shares -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
today -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
comes -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
back -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
US -X- _ B-TICKER
ordering -X- _ O
increased -X- _ O
economic -X- _ O
pressure -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Venezuelan -X- _ O
oil -X- _ O
shipments -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
carrying -X- _ O
out -X- _ O
airstrikes -X- _ O
against -X- _ O
Islamic -X- _ O
State -X- _ O
militants -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
northwest -X- _ O
Nigeria -X- _ B-GPE
at -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
request -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Nigeria -X- _ B-GPE
's -X- _ O
government. -X- _ O
Both -X- _ O
Venezuela -X- _ B-GPE
and -X- _ O
Nigeria -X- _ B-GPE
are -X- _ O
major -X- _ O
oil -X- _ O
producers. -X- _ O
While -X- _ B-PERSON
Nigeria -X- _ I-PERSON
's -X- _ O
oilfields -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
mainly -X- _ O
located -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
south -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
country -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
airstrikes -X- _ O
added -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
geopolitical -X- _ O
risks. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
White -X- _ O
House -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
ordered -X- _ O
US -X- _ B-TICKER
military -X- _ O
forces -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
focus -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
quarantine -X- _ O
" -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Venezuelan -X- _ O
oil -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
least -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
two -X- _ O
months -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
indicating -X- _ O
Washington -X- _ B-GPE
is -X- _ O
currently -X- _ O
more -X- _ O
interested -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
using -X- _ O
economic -X- _ O
rather -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
military -X- _ O
means -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
pressure -X- _ O
Caracas. -X- _ O
There -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
expectations -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
upcoming -X- _ O
FY27 -X- _ B-DATE
Budget -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
defence -X- _ O
budget -X- _ O
could -X- _ O
rise -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
20 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
. -X- _ O
India -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
push -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
significantly -X- _ O
higher -X- _ O
defence -X- _ O
allocation -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
fiscal -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Defence -X- _ O
Secretary -X- _ O
Rajesh -X- _ B-PERSON
Kumar -X- _ I-PERSON
Singh -X- _ I-PERSON
said -X- _ O
last -X- _ O
month. -X- _ O
Speaking -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
98th -X- _ O
Annual -X- _ B-EVENT
General -X- _ I-EVENT
Meeting -X- _ I-EVENT
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Federation -X- _ B-ORG
of -X- _ I-ORG
Indian -X- _ I-ORG
Chambers -X- _ I-ORG
of -X- _ I-ORG
Commerce -X- _ I-ORG
& -X- _ I-ORG
Industry -X- _ I-ORG
( -X- _ O
FICCI -X- _ B-TICKER
) -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
he -X- _ O
noted -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
country -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
traditionally -X- _ O
received -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
“10 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
higher -X- _ O
defence -X- _ O
allocation -X- _ O
every -X- _ O
year.” -X- _ O
“We -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
particularly -X- _ O
tough -X- _ O
neighbourhood -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
” -X- _ O
Singh -X- _ O
said. -X- _ O
“Will -X- _ O
be -X- _ O
asking -X- _ O
closer -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
20 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
higher -X- _ O
allocation -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
coming -X- _ O
budget.” -X- _ O
At -X- _ O
10:30 -X- _ O
am -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
December -X- _ O
26 -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Nifty -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
India -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
Defence -X- _ I-INSTRUMENT
index -X- _ O
was -X- _ O
trading -X- _ O
1 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
higher -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
7,870 -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
thus -X- _ O
extending -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
five-session -X- _ O
gains -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
6.5 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
. -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
index -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
still -X- _ O
14 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
lower -X- _ O
than -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
all-time -X- _ O
high -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Prabhudas -X- _ B-PERSON
Lilladher -X- _ I-PERSON
's -X- _ O
research -X- _ O
report -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Ultratech -X- _ B-ORG
Cement -X- _ I-ORG
We -X- _ O
upgrade -X- _ O
Ultratech -X- _ B-PERSON
Cement -X- _ I-PERSON
( -X- _ O
UTCEM -X- _ B-TICKER
) -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
‘BUY’ -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
we -X- _ O
expect -X- _ O
cement -X- _ O
pricing -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
improve -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
Jan’26 -X- _ O
led -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
strengthening -X- _ O
demand -X- _ B-METRIC
and -X- _ O
impending -X- _ O
pressure -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
industry -X- _ B-METRIC
margins -X- _ I-METRIC
due -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
current -X- _ O
weak -X- _ O
prices -X- _ O
& -X- _ O
elevated -X- _ O
pet -X- _ B-METRIC
coke -X- _ I-METRIC
prices. -X- _ I-METRIC
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ B-INSTRUMENT
has -X- _ O
also -X- _ O
corrected -X- _ O
~11 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
from -X- _ O
Aug’25 -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
account -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
muted -X- _ O
demand -X- _ O
amid -X- _ O
monsoon -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
GST -X- _ B-EVENT
rationalization -X- _ I-EVENT
limiting -X- _ O
price -X- _ O
hikes. -X- _ O
Cement -X- _ O
demand -X- _ B-METRIC
momentum -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
improved -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
H2FY26 -X- _ B-DATE
, -X- _ O
aided -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
rural -X- _ B-GPE
housing -X- _ I-GPE
, -X- _ O
commercial -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
urban -X- _ B-GPE
housing -X- _ I-GPE
demand. -X- _ O
While -X- _ O
several -X- _ O
infrastructure -X- _ O
projects -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
announced -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
activities -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
muted -X- _ O
post -X- _ O
monsoon. -X- _ O
Capex -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
roads -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
growing -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
Sep’25 -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
per -X- _ O
recent -X- _ O
GoI -X- _ O
spending -X- _ O
data. -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
expect -X- _ O
demand -X- _ B-METRIC
to -X- _ O
improve -X- _ O
across -X- _ O
regions -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
GoI -X- _ O
spending -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
infrastructure -X- _ O
improves -X- _ O
over -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
few -X- _ O
months. -X- _ O
Key -X- _ O
regions -X- _ O
such -X- _ O
as -X- _ O
South -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
East -X- _ O
where -X- _ O
stable -X- _ O
governments -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
formed -X- _ O
recently -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
drive -X- _ O
this -X- _ O
growth -X- _ O
; -X- _ O
while -X- _ O
demand -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
North -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Central -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
West -X- _ O
would -X- _ O
remain -X- _ O
stable. -X- _ O
This -X- _ O
would -X- _ O
reduce -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
gap -X- _ O
between -X- _ O
non-trade -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
trade -X- _ B-METRIC
prices -X- _ I-METRIC
, -X- _ O
which -X- _ O
has -X- _ O
increased -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
recent -X- _ O
months. -X- _ O
Trade -X- _ B-METRIC
prices -X- _ I-METRIC
have -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
largely -X- _ O
stable. -X- _ O
While -X- _ O
weak -X- _ O
rupee -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
higher -X- _ O
pet -X- _ B-METRIC
coke -X- _ I-METRIC
prices -X- _ I-METRIC
are -X- _ O
expected -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
impact -X- _ O
industry -X- _ B-METRIC
margins -X- _ I-METRIC
, -X- _ O
UTCEM -X- _ B-TICKER
would -X- _ O
benefit -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
higher -X- _ O
coal -X- _ O
share -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
logistics -X- _ O
optimization -X- _ O
aided -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
expanded -X- _ O
manufacturing -X- _ O
footprint -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
synergy -X- _ O
benefits -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
integration -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
acquired -X- _ O
capacities. -X- _ O
Outlook -X- _ B-PERSON
We -X- _ I-PERSON
expect -X- _ O
UTCEM -X- _ B-TICKER
volumes -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
clock -X- _ O
~12 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
CAGR -X- _ B-TICKER
over -X- _ O
FY25-28E -X- _ B-DATE
on -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
back -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
superior -X- _ O
execution -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
ramp -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
recent -X- _ O
inorganic -X- _ O
expansion. -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
have -X- _ O
tweaked -X- _ O
our -X- _ O
estimates -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
-6 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
/ -X- _ O
-1 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
/ -X- _ O
+4 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
for -X- _ O
FY26 -X- _ B-DATE
/ -X- _ I-DATE
27 -X- _ I-DATE
/ -X- _ I-DATE
28E -X- _ I-DATE
on -X- _ O
near-term -X- _ O
weak -X- _ O
cement -X- _ O
pricing -X- _ O
while -X- _ O
maintaining -X- _ O
volume -X- _ O
assumptions. -X- _ O
We -X- _ O
expect -X- _ O
EBITDA -X- _ B-METRIC
to -X- _ O
deliver -X- _ O
strong -X- _ O
24 -X- _ B-PERCENT
% -X- _ I-PERCENT
CAGR -X- _ B-TICKER
over -X- _ O
FY25-28E. -X- _ B-DATE
The -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
trading -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
EV -X- _ B-TICKER
of -X- _ O
16.4x -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
14.1x -X- _ O
FY27E -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
28E -X- _ O
EBITDA. -X- _ B-METRIC
We -X- _ O
upgrade -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
stock -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
‘BUY’ -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
‘Accumulate’ -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
revised -X- _ O
TP -X- _ B-TICKER
of -X- _ O
Rs13,625 -X- _ B-MONEY
( -X- _ O
Rs13,425 -X- _ B-MONEY
earlier -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
valuing -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
18x -X- _ O
EV -X- _ B-TICKER
of -X- _ O
Sep’27E -X- _ O
EBITDA. -X- _ B-METRIC
For -X- _ O
all -X- _ O
recommendations -X- _ O
report -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
click -X- _ O
here -X- _ O
Disclaimer -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
The -X- _ O
views -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
investment -X- _ O
tips -X- _ O
expressed -X- _ O
by -X- _ O
investment -X- _ O
experts -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
broking -X- _ O
houses -X- _ O
/ -X- _ O
rating -X- _ O
agencies -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
moneycontrol.com -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
own -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
and -X- _ O
not -X- _ O
that -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
website -X- _ O
or -X- _ O
its -X- _ O
management. -X- _ O
Moneycontrol.com -X- _ O
advises -X- _ O
users -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
check -X- _ O
with -X- _ O
certified -X- _ O
experts -X- _ O
before -X- _ O
taking -X- _ O
any -X- _ O
investment -X- _ O
decisions. -X- _ O
Ultratech -X- _ B-PERSON
Cement -X- _ I-PERSON
- -X- _ O
22122025 -X- _ O
- -X- _ O
prabhu -X- _ O