So O
I O
think O
that O
has O
changed O
everything O
quite O
a O
bit. O

In O
India, O
digital-first O
offerings O
from O
several O
leading O
banks O
are O
available, O
such O
as O
Kotak B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
and O
others. O

The O
central O
question, O
according O
to O
Pettit, O
is O
whether O
these O
cuts O
will O
be O
accompanied O
by O
economic O
weakness O
or O
if O
the O
US B-TICKER
economy O
will O
remain O
resilient. O

While O
the O
upturn O
may O
be O
relatively O
shallow, O
we O
do O
expect O
a O
recovery O
to O
continue, O
with O
the O
last O
quarter O
of O
the O
current O
fiscal O
also O
shaping O
up O
to O
be O
supportive O
for O
the O
segment. O

From O
a O
long-term O
perspective, O
rising O
government O
interest O
burdens O
strengthen O
gold’s O
role O
as O
a O
reliable O
store O
of O
value O
and O
a O
hedge O
against O
fiscal O
and O
monetary O
uncertainty. O

Globally, O
the O
markets O
of O
all O
asset O
classes O
will O
look O
for O
cues O
with O
respect O
to O
further O
rate O
cut O
path, O
jobs O
data, O
inflation O
and O
economic O
outlook O
from O
the O
minutes. O

As O
per O
a O
Moneycontrol B-ORG
analysis, O
15 O
new-age O
IPOs O
raised O
close O
to O
Rs B-MONEY
40,000 I-MONEY
crore I-MONEY
in O
2025, O
more O
than O
35 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
higher O
than O
the O
Rs B-MONEY
29,000 I-MONEY
crore I-MONEY
raised O
across O
13 O
listings O
in O
2024. O

Prabhudas B-PERSON
Lilladher's I-PERSON
research O
report O
on O
Apar B-ORG
Industries I-ORG
We O
interacted O
with O
the O
management O
of O
Apar B-ORG
Industries I-ORG
(APR) B-TICKER
to O
assess O
the O
domestic O
demand O
environment, O
the O
implications O
of O
US B-TICKER
reciprocal O
tariffs, O
and O
the O
company’s O
overall O
business O
outlook. O

The O
phrase’s O
purpose O
as O
a O
descriptive O
shorthand O
for O
a O
chronic O
economic O
phenomenon O
continues O
to O
be O
seen O
as O
a O
commentary O
on O
Hindus, O
as O
if O
only O
the O
Hindus O
were O
responsible O
for O
India's B-GPE
economic O
stagnation O
and O
the O
perceived O
failures O
of O
its O
statist O
economic O
model. O

Even B-PERSON
China, I-PERSON
despite O
its O
expansive O
surveillance O
apparatus, O
does O
not O
publicly O
mandate O
always-on, O
hardware-level O
location O
tracking O
on O
every O
smartphone. O

The O
spokesperson O
said O
the O
airline O
is O
making O
“very O
significant” O
progress O
in O
restoring O
flight O
schedules O
and O
strengthening O
customer O
support O
systems. O

Hooker I-PERSON
will O
also O
seek O
to O
deepen O
economic O
and O
commercial O
ties O
and O
boost O
US B-TICKER
exports, O
according O
to O
the O
statement, O
and O
foster O
collaboration O
in O
AI B-TICKER
and O
space O
exploration. O

The O
question O
is O
how O
India B-GPE
can O
capture O
this O
opportunity O
without O
weighing O
it O
down O
with O
premature O
or O
heavy-handed O
regulation. O

The O
goal O
of O
understanding O
risk O
is O
not O
to O
avoid O
debt O
funds. O

The O
company O
had O
fixed O
the O
price O
band O
at O
Rs B-MONEY
118-124 I-MONEY
per O
share. O

In O
the O
international B-GPE
markets, I-GPE
gold O
prices O
climbed O
by O
USD B-TICKER
165.4, O
or O
3.77 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent, I-PERCENT
during O
the O
past O
week. O

The O
market O
capitalisation O
of O
the O
company O
stands O
at O
Rs B-MONEY
4,243.49 I-MONEY
crore. I-MONEY

“I O
am O
sure O
we O
will O
address O
the O
trade O
imbalance O
in O
the O
near O
future O
and O
work O
collectively O
to O
eliminate, O
reduce O
and O
dilute O
trade O
barriers O
if O
any, O
work O
to O
create O
the O
right O
conditions O
to O
open O
more O
opportunities O
for O
businesses O
in O
both O
countries,” O
Commerce O
Minister O
Piyush B-PERSON
Goyal I-PERSON
said O
at O
an O
event O
in O
New B-GPE
Delhi I-GPE
on O
December B-DATE
4. I-DATE

This O
shifts O
the O
presumption O
at O
the O
heart O
of O
the O
Republic: O
from O
targeted O
scrutiny O
of O
suspects O
to O
ambient O
tracking O
of O
everyone. O

Additionally, O
the O
council O
exempted O
UHT O
milk, B-PRODUCT
paneer, B-PRODUCT
chhena, B-PRODUCT
and O
Indian B-PRODUCT
breads I-PRODUCT
at O
zero O
per O
cent, O
reducing O
input O
costs O
by O
7-13 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent I-PERCENT
and O
enabling O
farmers O
to O
save O
Rs B-MONEY
50,000 I-MONEY
to O
Rs B-MONEY
1 I-MONEY
lakh I-MONEY
on O
tractor O
purchases. O

Over O
the O
last O
few O
months, O
we O
have O
started O
to O
see O
early O
green O
shoots O
of O
recovery, O
both O
in O
key O
lead O
indicators O
and O
in O
commercial O
vehicle O
sales O
data. O

Do O
you O
think O
the O
commercial O
vehicle O
segment O
within O
the O
auto O
space O
will O
make O
a O
strong O
comeback O
next O
year? O

Outlook O
CIFC B-TICKER
remains O
a O
robust O
franchise, O
with O
an O
expected O
CAGR B-ORG
of O
~20% B-PERCENT
in O
AUM B-METRIC
and O
~25% B-PERCENT
in O
PAT B-METRIC
over O
FY25-28, B-DATE
alongside O
projected O
RoA/RoE B-METRIC
of O
2.7%/20% B-PERCENT
in O
FY28. B-DATE

Data O
period O
Jan B-DATE
1 I-DATE
to I-DATE
Dec I-DATE
22, I-DATE
2025 I-DATE
closing O
period O
has O
been O
considered.) O
Sectoral O
Trends: O
Metals O
shine, O
Realty O
cracks O
2025 O
has O
seen O
significant O
divergence O
in O
sectoral O
performance. O

InterGlobe B-ORG
Aviation, I-ORG
Bharat B-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and O
ETERNAL O
were O
among O
the O
major O
laggards O
in O
the O
Nifty50 O
pack, O
declining O
up O
to O
7 B-PERCENT
percent, I-PERCENT
while O
HDFC B-ORG
Life I-ORG
Insurance I-ORG
Company I-ORG
and O
Tech B-ORG
Mahindra I-ORG
were O
among O
the O
major O
gainers, O
rising O
up O
to O
1 B-PERCENT
percent. I-PERCENT

Investors O
are O
wagering O
that O
a O
new O
Federal B-PERSON
Reserve I-PERSON
chair O
and O
the O
release O
of O
delayed O
US B-TICKER
economic O
data O
this O
month O
will O
support O
President B-PERSON
Donald I-PERSON
Trump’s I-PERSON
calls O
for O
monetary O
easing. O

Outlook B-PERSON
We I-PERSON
retain O
BUY B-TICKER
on O
BoB B-ORG
while O
raising O
our O
TP B-TICKER
to O
Rs350 B-MONEY
(from O
Rs330), B-MONEY
rolling O
forward O
SA B-TICKER
bank O
to O
1x O
Dec-27E B-DATE
ABV B-TICKER
and O
subsidiaries/investment O
at O
Rs15/sh. B-MONEY

Goenka O
said O
the O
tyre O
maker O
remains O
very O
optimistic O
about O
growth O
prospects O
going O
ahead. O

It O
found O
no O
restriction O
on O
consumer O
choice O
or O
competition, O
noting O
that O
users O
can O
install O
third-party O
solutions O
and O
established O
rivals O
remain O
active O
in O
the O
market. O

did O
not O
reach O
a O
compromise O
on O
a O
possible O
peace O
deal O
for O
Ukraine B-GPE
after O
a O
five-hour O
meeting O
between O
President B-PERSON
Vladimir I-PERSON
Putin I-PERSON
and O
U.S. B-GPE

A O
recovery O
is O
clearly O
underway, O
and O
we O
believe O
the O
segment O
is O
already O
in O
the O
process O
of O
picking O
up O
momentum. O

Q3FY26 O
is O
expected O
to O
remain O
muted O
due O
to O
elevated O
raw O
material O
prices O
and O
slower O
order O
finalizations, O
followed O
by O
a O
recovery O
in O
Q4FY26. O

On O
Comex, O
gold B-INSTRUMENT
futures I-INSTRUMENT
for O
December O
delivery O
slipped O
by O
USD B-MONEY
20.1, I-MONEY
or O
0.47 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent, I-PERCENT
to O
USD B-MONEY
4,219.2 I-MONEY
per O
ounce. O

The O
shares O
of O
the O
IT O
firm O
rose O
to O
Rs B-MONEY
1,711 I-MONEY
apiece O
in O
the O
early O
trading O
hours O
of O
Monday, O
snapping O
a O
three-session O
losing O
streak. O

Major O
launches O
included O
the O
Pradhan B-PRODUCT
Mantri I-PRODUCT
Dhan-Dhaanya I-PRODUCT
Krishi I-PRODUCT
Yojana I-PRODUCT
(over O
Rs B-MONEY
35,000 I-MONEY
crore I-MONEY
targeting O
100 O
low-productivity O
districts O
and O
1.7 O
crore O
farmers), O
Rs B-MONEY
11,440-crore I-MONEY
National B-PRODUCT
Pulses I-PRODUCT
Mission, I-PRODUCT
MSP B-TICKER
hikes O
for O
rabi O
crops, O
and O
continuation O
of O
the O
Modified B-PRODUCT
Interest I-PRODUCT
Subvention I-PRODUCT
Scheme. I-PRODUCT

Strategy: O
Buy O
Target: O
Rs B-MONEY
1,880 I-MONEY
Stop-Loss: O
Rs B-MONEY
1,660 I-MONEY

Renewed O
momentum O
in O
the O
second O
half O
What O
stands O
out O
most O
is O
the O
renewed O
momentum O
we O
witnessed O
in O
the O
latter O
part O
of O
the O
year. O

"Raw O
material O
prices O
have O
been O
largely O
flat. O

The O
Governor O
noted O
that O
inflation O
has O
become O
more O
generalised O
on O
the O
downside, O
with O
food O
deflation O
deepening O
and O
precious-metal-driven O
pressures O
easing. O

Often, O
SEBI B-ORG
also O
starts O
parallel O
proceedings O
under O
the O
Intermediaries O
Regulations, O
where O
possible O
directions O
include O
suspension O
or O
cancellation O
of O
registration. O

ICICI B-TICKER
Prudential I-ORG
Asset I-ORG
Management I-ORG
Company O
is O
preparing O
a O
series O
of O
fund O
launches O
under O
the O
newly O
created, O
SEBI-approved B-ORG
SIF B-TICKER
category, O
with O
Managing O
Director O
and O
CEO O
Nimesh B-PERSON
Shah I-PERSON
expressing O
optimism O
about O
its O
long-term O
potential O
while O
emphasising O
that O
early O
traction O
will O
take O
time. O

Once O
he O
had O
even O
questioned O
why O
his O
uncle O
should O
continue O
to O
lead O
the O
party O
at O
his O
age. O

Brokerage O
firm O
Elara B-ORG
Capital I-ORG
has O
noted O
that O
IHCL’s B-TICKER
recent O
hotel O
sign-ups O
are O
increasingly O
skewed O
towards O
the O
premium O
Taj O
brand, O
which O
typically O
generates O
higher O
fees O
per O
room O
compared O
with O
mid-scale O
and O
budget O
formats. O

Signzy’s B-PRODUCT
VC I-PRODUCT
tool I-PRODUCT
allows O
banks, B-ORG
insurance B-ORG
companies I-ORG
and O
other O
financial O
services O
providers O
to O
go O
a O
few O
steps O
further O
and O
use O
secure O
video O
conferencing O
for O
other O
processes O
that O
otherwise O
necessitate O
a O
face-to-face O
interaction O
with O
the O
customer, O
inside O
the O
branch O
or O
at O
the O
customer’s O
premises. O

When O
households O
know O
that O
treatment O
costs O
will O
not O
erode O
their O
savings, O
they O
consume, O
invest O
and O
plan O
with O
more O
confidence. O

Currency O
movement O
can O
provide O
a O
near-term O
tailwind O
and O
may O
result O
in O
a O
near O
term O
benefit O
for O
these O
sectors. O

The O
CCI’s B-TICKER
AI B-TICKER
market O
study O
finds O
that O
AI B-TICKER
adoption O
has O
enhanced O
consumer O
welfare O
by O
improving O
service O
quality, O
personalisation, O
and O
access, O
and O
by O
expanding O
consumer O
choice O
through O
new O
and O
customised O
offerings O
The O
risk O
of O
regulating O
too O
early O
is O
that O
consumers O
end O
up O
paying O
more, O
while O
innovation O
slows, O
derailing O
India’s O
AI B-TICKER
growth O
story. O

She O
noted O
that O
the O
latest O
US B-TICKER
economic O
data O
added O
to O
the O
cautious O
tone, O
with O
the O
Institute B-ORG
for I-ORG
Supply I-ORG
Management I-ORG
reporting O
that O
manufacturing O
contracted O
for O
a O
ninth O
consecutive O
month, O
adding O
pressure O
on O
the O
Fed O
to O
ease O
policy. O

She O
will O
be O
in O
New B-GPE
Delhi I-GPE
and O
Bengaluru B-GPE
and O
will O
meet O
with O
senior O
Indian O
officials O
including O
Foreign O
Secretary O
Vikram B-PERSON
Misri. I-PERSON

But O
turning O
every O
citizen O
into O
a O
traceable O
coordinate O
is O
surrendering O
to O
the O
illusion O
that O
safety O
can O
be O
purchased O
by O
trading O
away O
liberty. O

The O
RBI B-ORG
expects O
Q1 B-DATE
and I-DATE
Q2 I-DATE
FY27 I-DATE
growth O
at O
6.7 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
and O
6.8 B-PERCENT
percent, I-PERCENT
driven O
by O
strong O
investment O
activity, O
robust O
rural O
demand O
and O
steadily O
improving O
urban O
consumption. O

The O
index O
has O
now O
gained O
around O
5 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
in O
eight O
sessions O
of O
gains O
so O
far. O

The O
unpredictability O
also O
helps O
minimize O
speculation O
in O
the O
market, O
according O
to O
G. B-PERSON

The O
shares B-INSTRUMENT
of O
Lenskart B-ORG
Solutions I-ORG
fell O
more O
than O
3 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
on O
December B-DATE
8 I-DATE
after O
the O
one-month O
shareholder O
lock-in O
period O
came O
to O
an O
end. O

Fertiliser O
Secretary O
Rajat B-PERSON
Kumar I-PERSON
Mishra I-PERSON
said O
there O
is O
robust O
availability O
of O
key O
soil O
nutrients O
through O
domestic O
production O
and O
imports O
from O
Saudi B-GPE
Arabia, I-GPE
Russia, B-GPE
and O
Morocco. B-GPE

The O
stock O
is O
up O
more O
than O
56 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
in O
2025 O
so O
far. O

Why O
are O
gold O
prices O
rising? O

Why O
are O
gold O
prices O
rising? O

(Kailash B-PERSON
Kulkarni I-PERSON
is O
CEO, O
HSBC B-ORG
MF.) I-ORG
Views O
are O
personal O
and O
do O
not O
represent O
the O
stand O
of O
this O
organisation. O

The O
issue O
opens O
on O
December I-DATE
12 I-DATE
and O
closes O
on O
December B-DATE
16. I-DATE

of O
shares O
(as O
a O
% O
of O
the O
total O
sh. O

“With O
almost O
a O
$7 B-MONEY
difference O
between O
the O
price O
of O
silver B-INSTRUMENT
on O
Comex O
and O
Shanghai B-GPE
(stock O
exchanges), O
the O
global O
arbitrage O
system O
and O
price O
discovery O
mechanism O
of O
silver B-INSTRUMENT
has O
collapsed. O

A O
pause O
in O
the O
next O
policy O
in O
February O
is O
more O
likely, O
given O
the O
fact O
that O
the O
policy O
stance O
continues O
to O
be O
neutral, O
and O
the O
MPC B-TICKER
might O
want O
to O
see O
improved O
transmission O
of O
the O
cumulative O
rate O
cuts O
carried O
out O
so O
far. O

As O
part O
of O
the O
somewhat O
asymmetric O
deals O
(biased O
in O
favor O
of O
the O
US) B-TICKER
with O
Japan, B-GPE
South B-GPE
Korea I-GPE
and O
the O
European B-GPE
Union, I-GPE
the O
administration O
has O
claimed O
to O
have O
received O
promises O
of O
hundreds O
of O
billions O
of O
dollars O
of O
investments O
in O
the O
American O
economy, O
even O
though O
it O
is O
well O
understood O
that O
such O
investments O
widen O
the O
US B-TICKER
trade O
deficit. O

“If O
I O
am O
charging O
less, O
my O
probability O
of O
meeting O
benchmark O
is O
higher. O

And B-PERSON
Selling I-PERSON
Expenses------R I-PERSON
& O
D O
Expenses------Provisions B-PERSON
And I-PERSON
Contingencies------Exp. I-PERSON

This O
marks O
a O
sharp O
recovery O
from O
Friday, O
when O
the O
carrier O
ran O
just O
over O
700 O
flights O
as O
part O
of O
a O
deliberate O
network O
“reboot.” O
The O
airline O
said O
the O
scaled-down O
schedule O
was O
necessary O
to O
reset O
rosters, O
systems, O
and O
overall O
network O
planning O
to O
stabilise O
operations. O

2025 O
was O
a O
testament O
to O
the O
enduring O
resilience O
of O
Indian O
equity O
markets. O

It O
has O
been O
designed O
for O
enabling O
front-end O
processes O
that O
necessitate O
a O
face-to-face O
conversation O
with O
the O
customer. O

As O
one O
of O
the O
outcomes, O
RBI, B-TICKER
DPIIT B-TICKER
and O
MoF B-TICKER
will O
look O
at O
the O
change O
of O
ownership O
holding/control O
of O
listed O
fintech O
companies O
to O
enable O
them O
to O
be O
in-sync O
with O
regulatory O
compliance, O
the O
ministry O
said O
in O
a O
statement. O

According O
to O
him, O
key O
drivers O
will O
include O
progress O
in O
India–US B-GPE
trade O
talks, O
rupee O
stability, O
FII B-TICKER
trends, O
and O
movements O
in O
commodity O
prices. O

India’s B-GPE
largest O
airline O
has O
been O
for O
the O
past O
six O
days O
cancelling O
hundreds O
of O
flights, O
including O
more O
than O
650 O
on O
Sunday O
out O
of O
around O
2,300 O
daily O
flights O
it O
operates, O
throwing O
travel O
plans O
into O
disarray O
for O
tens O
of O
thousands O
of O
passengers.The O
disruption O
left O
many O
missing B-EVENT
critical I-EVENT
meetings, I-EVENT
job I-EVENT
interviews I-EVENT
and I-EVENT
even I-EVENT
their I-EVENT
own I-EVENT
wedding I-EVENT
receptions, I-EVENT
while O
some O
stranded O
travellers O
were O
reportedly O
dealing O
with O
medical O
emergencies.With O
IndiGo B-ORG
commanding O
over O
65 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent I-PERCENT
of O
India’s B-GPE
domestic O
market, O
the O
disruptions O
set O
off O
a O
nationwide O
domino O
effect, O
overwhelming O
airports B-GPE
and O
leaving O
rival O
carriers O
unable O
to O
absorb O
the O
surge O
of O
displaced O
travellers. O

The O
counter O
extended O
losses O
after O
Kotak B-INSTRUMENT
Institutional I-INSTRUMENT
Equities I-INSTRUMENT
flagged O
concerns O
over O
inconsistencies O
in O
the O
company’s O
related-party O
disclosures. O

However, O
can O
virtual O
events O
build O
humanly-relationships, O
especially O
in O
domains O
like O
fintech O
where O
automation O
is O
prevalent? O

Gold B-INSTRUMENT
logged O
its O
fourth O
straight O
monthly O
rise, O
while O
silver B-INSTRUMENT
notched O
its O
seventh O
consecutive O
monthly O
advance O
and O
its O
biggest O
monthly O
gain O
of O
2025 O
at O
18.7 B-PERCENT
percent. I-PERCENT

Myntra B-PERSON
Beauty, I-PERSON
which O
has O
emerged O
among O
key O
growth O
engines O
for O
the O
platform, O
witnessed O
robust O
momentum, O
growing O
at O
nearly O
2X O
of O
the O
online O
beauty O
market O
and O
continues O
to O
gain O
market O
share. O

Ambuja B-ORG
Cements I-ORG
- O
23122025 O
- O
moti O

India’s B-GPE
recent O
free O
trade O
agreements O
with O
Australia B-GPE
and O
the O
United B-GPE
Arab I-GPE
Emirates I-GPE
have O
produced O
a O
mixed—but O
largely O
encouraging—outcome, O
with O
Indian O
exporters O
gaining O
market O
share O
across O
a O
substantial O
portion O
of O
product O
categories, O
even O
as O
meaningful O
losses O
persist O
in O
several O
others. O

“This O
milestone O
represents O
India’s O
growing O
confidence O
in O
shaping O
its O
own O
defence O
future. O

Are O
you O
focusing O
more O
on O
tier O
2 O
cities? O

And O
what O
comes O
after O
is O
a O
well-known O
and O
worn O
lesson O
of O
history O
– O
a O
transition O
of O
a O
society O
of O
demos O
into O
that O
of O
helots. O

If O
you O
look O
at O
the O
track O
record, O
the O
Nifty B-INSTRUMENT
has O
delivered O
positive O
returns O
in O
every O
calendar O
year O
for O
the O
last O
10 O
years, O
which O
is O
quite O
rare O
and O
something O
very O
few O
equity O
markets O
globally O
have O
managed O
to O
achieve. O

Housing O
loans, O
consumption B-INSTRUMENT
credit, I-INSTRUMENT
personal B-INSTRUMENT
loans, I-INSTRUMENT
and O
buy-now-pay-later B-PRODUCT
products I-PRODUCT
have O
fostered O
a O
new O
belief O
that O
access O
matters O
more O
than O
accumulation. O

JM B-TICKER
Financial O
said O
that O
the O
valuation O
looks O
rich O
given O
Encora’s O
7 O
– O
10 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
growth O
profile, O
CNBC-TV18 B-TICKER
reported. O

Citi O
maintained O
a O
‘buy’ O
call O
with O
a O
Rs B-MONEY
6,500 I-MONEY
target O
price, O
while O
Morgan B-ORG
Stanley I-ORG
trimmed O
its O
target O
and O
cut O
EPS B-TICKER
estimates O
for O
FY27 B-DATE
and O
FY28 B-DATE
by O
20 B-PERCENT
percent, I-PERCENT
citing O
higher O
crew-related O
costs O
due O
to O
the O
new O
duty O
norms. O

Our O
view O
is O
after O
minor O
correction O
we O
have O
a O
high O
probability O
for O
Bank B-PERSON
Nifty I-PERSON
to O
cross O
60114 O
and O
reach O
61050—62540—63470 O
area,” O
Ventura O
said. O

SHOWCAUSE: O
DGCA B-TICKER
on O
December O
6 O
issued O
show-cause O
notices O
to O
IndiGo O
CEO O
Pieter B-PERSON
Elbers I-PERSON
and O
Accountable O
Manager O
Isidro B-PERSON
Porqueras, I-PERSON
seeking O
explanations O
within O
24 O
hours O
on O
the O
massive O
flight O
disruptions.The O
notices O
mentioned O
that O
the O
primary O
cause O
of O
the O
flight O
disruptions O
is O
the O
non-provisioning O
of O
adequate O
arrangements O
to O
cater O
to O
the O
revised O
requirements O
for O
smooth O
implementation O
of O
the O
approved O
FDTL B-TICKER
scheme O
for O
the O
airline. O

But O
implementation O
is O
uneven, O
and O
workers O
say O
platform O
behaviour O
on O
the O
ground O
has O
barely O
changed. O

Credit B-EVENT
events I-EVENT
don’t O
happen O
daily, O
but O
when O
they O
do, O
impact O
feels O
sudden O
and O
emotional. O

Ryan's O
optimism O
extended O
to O
the O
widespread O
adoption O
of O
QR B-TICKER
payments O
in O
India, B-GPE
attributing O
inspiration O
to O
local O
fintech O
innovation. O

Sachin B-PERSON
Jain, I-PERSON
regional O
chief O
executive O
for O
India B-GPE
at O
the O
WGC, B-TICKER
told O
The B-ORG
Economic I-ORG
Times I-ORG
that O
gold B-INSTRUMENT
continues O
to O
be O
a O
core O
asset O
for O
Indian O
households, O
and O
digital O
formats O
improve O
accessibility O
through O
fractional O
ownership, O
market-linked O
pricing, O
and O
reduced O
concerns O
over O
storage O
and O
purity. O

The O
Hon’ble O
Supreme O
Court O
has O
not O
examined O
the O
merits O
of O
my O
claims, O
nor O
has O
it O
closed O
any O
issue. O

Inflation O
outlook O
revised O
sharply O
lower O
following O
a O
historic O
collapse O
in O
food O
prices: O
FY26 B-DATE
CPI B-TICKER
inflation O
has O
been O
cut O
to O
2.0 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
(from O
2.6 B-PERCENT
percent), I-PERCENT
with O
Q3 O
at O
0.6 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
and O
Q4 O
at O
2.9 B-PERCENT
percent. I-PERCENT

Gold’s B-INSTRUMENT
recent O
run O
has O
been O
driven O
by O
its O
haven O
appeal O
amid O
escalating O
frictions O
in O
Venezuela, B-GPE
where O
the O
US B-TICKER
has O
blockaded O
oil O
tankers. O

Key O
outcome O
One O
of O
the O
main O
outcomes O
of O
the O
meet O
was O
that O
there O
will O
be O
monthly O
calls O
between O
the O
regulator O
and O
fintechs O
wherein, O
the O
latter O
can O
seek O
clarity O
on O
any O
regulations O
and O
get O
feedback. O

The O
scale O
of O
these O
obligations O
is O
also O
evident O
when O
compared O
with O
the O
company’s O
cash O
position. O

I O
am O
focused O
on O
a O
profitable O
growth O
in O
every O
business O
of O
mine. O

Banks O
are O
parking O
more O
metal O
in O
the O
US B-TICKER
to O
insure O
against O
the O
risk O
of O
tariffs, O
while O
exports O
to O
China O
have O
been O
robust O
as O
demand O
grows O
and O
contracts O
begin O
trading O
on O
the O
Guangzhou B-ORG
Futures I-ORG
Exchange. I-ORG

of O
shares O
(as O
a O
% O
of O
the O
total O
Share B-PERSON
Cap. I-PERSON

Hindustan B-ORG
Zinc I-ORG
shares O
gained O
nearly O
2 B-PERCENT
percent, I-PERCENT
while O
APL B-TICKER
Apollo B-ORG
Tubes I-ORG
and O
JSW B-ORG
Steel I-ORG
shares O
gained O
more O
than O
1 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
each. O

"Silver’s B-INSTRUMENT
higher O
beta O
versus O
gold B-INSTRUMENT
means O
corrections O
tend O
to O
be O
faster O
and O
deeper. O

This O
build-up O
comes O
as O
late-stage O
private O
capital O
remains O
constrained O
and O
more O
scaled O
companies O
are O
considering O
public O
markets O
as O
their O
most O
realistic O
route O
for O
funding, O
liquidity O
and O
valuation O
discovery. O

In O
BJP, B-ORG
leaders O
retire O
at O
75, O
when O
are O
you O
going O
to O
stop? O

Given O
the O
government’s O
majority O
holding, O
periodic O
stake O
dilution O
is O
important O
for O
improving O
free O
float O
and O
enhancing O
long-term O
institutional O
participation. O

With O
most O
portfolios' O
average O
gold O
allocation O
under O
5 B-PERCENT
percent, I-PERCENT
investors O
would O
need O
to O
buy O
a O
lot O
more O
yellow O
metal O
to O
increase O
their O
gold O
holdings O
to O
20 B-PERCENT
percent. I-PERCENT

"The O
data O
will O
influence O
expectations O
about O
the O
Fed's O
rate-cut O
path, O
which, O
in O
turn, O
will O
drive O
the O
US B-TICKER
Dollar O
and O
provide O
a O
short-term O
direction O
to O
the O
commodity O
prices," O
Trivedi O
added. O

A O
single O
disruption—job O
loss O
or O
medical O
emergency—can O
cause O
stress. O

Under O
Prime O
Minister O
Narendra B-PERSON
Modi, I-PERSON
the O
government B-ORG
pushed O
through O
structural O
reforms O
across O
taxation, O
labour, O
trade, O
energy O
and O
regulation, O
signalling O
a O
decisive O
shift O
towards O
scale, O
clarity O
and O
long-term O
competitiveness. O

The O
regulator O
has O
set O
up O
a O
four-member O
committee O
to O
examine O
why O
some O
carriers O
failed O
to O
accurately O
forecast O
crew O
availability, O
complete O
training, O
and O
recalibrate O
schedules O
despite O
being O
notified O
months O
in O
advance. O

Geopolitical O
tensions O
that O
have O
risen O
in O
recent O
weeks O
have O
also O
enhanced O
the O
haven O
appeal O
of O
gold B-INSTRUMENT
and O
silver. B-INSTRUMENT

Defence B-INSTRUMENT
shares I-INSTRUMENT
rose O
for O
fifth O
consecutive O
session O
on O
December O
26 O
amid O
geopolitical O
tensions O
flaring O
up O
in O
different O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
and O
year-end O
Defence B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Council I-ORG
meeting O
today. O

But O
this O
time O
when O
you O
apply, O
you O
will O
not O
have O
a O
vehicle O
like O
Chaitanya B-PERSON
(in O
the O
microfinance O
business), O
right? O

This O
was O
the O
2nd O
consecutive O
quarter O
of O
double-digit O
growth O
in O
the O
India B-GPE
core O
business O
across O
both O
tea O
and O
salt. O

Mass O
surveillance O
may O
begin O
as O
an O
anti-fraud O
tool, O
but O
it O
rarely O
stays O
that O
way. O

The O
allotments O
are O
likely O
to O
be O
finalized O
by O
December O
8, O
and O
the O
shares O
are O
scheduled O
to O
be O
listed O
on O
stock O
exchanges O
BSE O
and O
NSE O
on O
December I-DATE
10. I-DATE

“When O
the O
markets O
corrected, O
the O
SIPs O
didn’t O
stop. O

The B-INSTRUMENT
Nifty I-INSTRUMENT
MNC I-INSTRUMENT
index O
also O
saw O
some O
improvement O
in O
momentum, O
but O
the O
relative O
strength O
continues O
to O
decline. O

For O
instance, O
frozen O
shrimp O
exports O
exceed O
$120 B-MONEY
million I-MONEY
with O
a O
market O
share O
of O
about O
35 B-PERCENT
percent, I-PERCENT
while O
roughly O
$70 B-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
black O
tea O
exports O
translates O
to O
a O
share O
below O
30 B-PERCENT
percent. I-PERCENT

"The O
2025 O
festive O
season O
(September-October) O
proved O
exceptionally O
strong, O
with O
total O
retail O
sales O
crossing O
Rs B-MONEY
6 I-MONEY
lakh I-MONEY
crore I-MONEY
($67 B-MONEY
billion), I-MONEY
aided O
by O
substantial O
discounts O
from O
both O
online O
and O
offline O
retailers,"according O
to O
the O
Confederation B-ORG
of I-ORG
All I-ORG
India I-ORG
Traders. I-ORG

Given O
these O
factors, O
real B-METRIC
GDP I-METRIC
growth I-METRIC
forecasts O
by O
RBI B-ORG
are O
as O
follows: O
FY26: B-DATE
7.30 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
(6.80 B-PERCENT
percent) I-PERCENT
; O
Q3FY26: B-DATE
7.00 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
(6.40 B-PERCENT
percent); I-PERCENT
Q4FY26: B-DATE
6.50 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
(6.20 B-PERCENT
percent); I-PERCENT
Q1FY27: B-DATE
6.70 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
(6.40 B-PERCENT
percent); I-PERCENT
Q2FY27: B-DATE
6.80 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
with O
risks O
evenly O
balanced. O

JM B-TICKER
Financial O
said O
that O
the O
valuation O
looks O
rich O
given O
Encora’s O
7 B-PERCENT
– I-PERCENT
10 I-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
growth O
profile, O
CNBC-TV18 B-ORG
reported. O

Regulatory O
tweaks O
rarely O
break O
portfolios, O
but O
they O
can O
influence O
post-tax O
outcome. O

in O
New B-GPE
York. I-GPE

Reimagining O
e-lifestyle O
shopping O
with O
Speed: O
Myntra O
is O
accelerating O
its O
efforts O
on O
rapid O
fashion O
delivery O
with O
M-Now, O
the O
speed O
delivery O
service O
starting O
30 O
minutes, O
offering O
fast, O
premium O
shopping O
for O
digital-first O
customers O
who O
value O
speed. O

Despite O
lower O
growth, O
COFORGE O
is O
acquiring O
Encora O
at O
3.9X O
EV/sales B-TICKER
and O
~21x O
EV/EBITDA, B-TICKER
in O
line O
with O
COFORGE O
’s O
multiples, O
which O
appears O
expensive. O

The O
sustained O
selling O
pressure O
dented O
investor O
sentiment O
and O
capped O
any O
meaningful O
upside O
in O
domestic O
stocks. O

Elections O
to O
29 O
municipal O
corporations O
across O
Maharashtra, B-GPE
including O
the O
Pimpri-Chinchwad B-GPE
and O
Pune B-GPE
civic O
bodies, O
will O
be O
held O
on O
January O
15, O
and O
votes O
will O
be O
counted O
the O
next O
day. O

The O
revised O
FDTL B-TICKER
norms O
brought O
into O
effect O
a O
stricter O
regime O
aimed O
at O
reducing O
pilot O
fatigue O
and O
enhancing O
operational O
safety. O

As O
every O
market O
forecaster O
and O
their O
uncle O
begin O
to O
predict O
2026, O
central O
bankers O
must O
clean O
up O
their O
models O
or O
else, O
join O
a O
group O
of O
shamans O
offering O
weird O
predictions. O

How O
the O
CCI B-TICKER
has O
approached O
tech O
integration O
The O
CCI B-TICKER
has O
been O
an O
active O
voice O
in O
this O
debate. O

Give O
us O
a O
few O
months, O
we O
have O
some O
things O
we're O
doing O
and O
we O
are O
hoping O
it O
will O
work. O

The O
stock's O
P/E O
ratio O
currently O
stands O
at O
around O
31. O

"I O
want O
more O
players O
in O
the O
industry. O

Both O
partners O
must O
do O
it. O

The O
stock O
rose O
9.54 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
to O
an O
intraday O
high O
of O
Rs B-MONEY
110.36 I-MONEY
on O
the O
NSE. B-ORG

Industry O
estimates O
suggest O
that O
digital B-INSTRUMENT
gold I-INSTRUMENT
purchases O
stood O
at O
about O
8 O
tonnes O
in O
2024, O
underscoring O
the O
pace O
of O
growth O
this O
year. O

By O
the O
year O
end, O
global O
volatility O
has O
forced O
the O
hand O
of O
the O
central O
bank, O
making O
it O
become O
a O
regular O
presence O
in O
both O
forex O
and O
the O
bond O
market. O

Silver O
edged O
higher. O

The B-EVENT
All I-EVENT
India I-EVENT
Debt I-EVENT
and I-EVENT
Investment I-EVENT
Survey I-EVENT
is O
scheduled O
to O
run O
from O
July B-DATE
2026 I-DATE
to I-DATE
June I-DATE
2027, I-DATE
with O
results O
expected O
in O
the O
second O
half O
of O
2027. O

and O
promoter O
group)------- O
Per. O

At O
Jet B-ORG
Airways I-ORG
during O
2018–19, B-DATE
clearance-related O
issues O
surrounding O
foreign O
executives O
reportedly O
complicated O
senior-level O
changes. O

Entry-level O
roles, O
already O
under O
pressure O
from O
automation O
and O
onshore O
hiring, O
will O
find O
it O
harder O
to O
clear O
the O
cap. O

"For O
silver O
specifically, O
strong O
industrial O
demand, O
supply B-METRIC
tightness, I-METRIC
and O
safe-haven B-METRIC
demand I-METRIC
have O
helped O
sustain O
price O
strength. O

"The O
easing O
labor O
market O
in O
the O
U.S. O

This O
approach O
speeds O
up O
compensation, O
reduces O
litigation O
costs O
and O
meaningfully O
lowers O
MACT B-TICKER
workloads. O

Krishnan, I-PERSON
Secretary, O
Ministry B-ORG
of I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Information I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
(MeitY), O
T. B-PERSON

After O
all, O
we O
did O
not O
rebel O
against O
the O
British O
Raj O
to O
escape O
becoming O
Macaulay-Putras O
to O
gain O
our O
freedom O
only O
to O
become O
Orwell-Putras O
75 O
years O
later. O

Vaults O
in O
London O
have O
drawn O
sizable O
inflows O
since O
the O
October O
squeeze, O
though O
much O
of O
the O
world’s O
readily O
available O
silver O
remains O
in O
New B-GPE
York I-GPE
as O
traders O
await O
the O
outcome O
of O
a O
US B-TICKER
Commerce O
Department O
probe O
into O
whether O
imports O
of O
critical O
minerals O
pose O
a O
national O
security O
risk. O

Ajit, O
who O
had O
taken O
oath O
as O
Deputy B-PERSON
Chief I-PERSON
Minister I-PERSON
thrice O
in O
four O
years, O
had O
repeatedly O
slammed O
his O
uncle, O
a O
four-time O
Chief B-PERSON
Minister I-PERSON
of O
the O
state. O

Ajit, O
who O
split O
his O
uncle O
Sharad B-PERSON
Pawar's I-PERSON
Nationalist B-PERSON
Congress I-PERSON
Party I-PERSON
and O
joined O
hands O
with O
the O
BJP B-TICKER
and O
Eknath B-PERSON
Shinde's I-PERSON
Shiv B-PERSON
Sena I-PERSON
in O
2023, O
had O
rebelled O
after O
making O
his O
misgivings O
clear O
about O
his O
uncle's O
staying O
at O
the O
helm O
of O
the O
party O
despite O
his O
advancing O
age. O

At O
11:25 O
am O
on O
December O
29, O
Sigachi O
shares O
were O
trading O
5.5% B-PERCENT
lower O
at O
Rs B-MONEY
32.07 I-MONEY
apiece. O

With O
this O
emerges O
the O
need O
for O
detailed O
guidance O
on O
every O
facet O
of O
statutory O
GAAR. B-TICKER

The O
company O
further O
stated O
that O
there O
is O
no O
change O
in O
business O
strategy, O
operating O
performance, O
or O
guidance, O
and O
reiterated O
confidence O
in O
delivering O
on O
its O
stated O
growth, B-METRIC
profitability, B-METRIC
and O
asset B-METRIC
quality I-METRIC
objectives. O

Instead O
of O
putting O
it O
all O
into O
equity O
on O
day O
one, O
you O
park O
it O
in O
a O
liquid B-INSTRUMENT
fund I-INSTRUMENT
and O
slowly O
shift O
it O
into O
equity. O

The O
price O
band O
for O
the O
maiden O
public O
issue O
of O
the O
company O
was O
set O
at O
Rs B-MONEY
123-130 I-MONEY
per O
share. O

Launched O
a O
year O
ago, O
M-Now O
is O
a O
key O
growth O
driver, O
attracting O
new O
customers O
and O
fueling O
demand, O
clocking O
10% B-PERCENT
of O
orders O
in O
its O
live O
locations, O
boosting O
platform O
affinity O
and O
growth O
with O
80 O
dark O
stores O
across O
the O
cities O
it's O
live O
and O
expanding O
rapidly. O

The O
new O
facility O
will O
join O
Lockheed B-ORG
Martin’s I-ORG
global O
network O
of O
Certified B-PRODUCT
Service I-PRODUCT
Centres I-PRODUCT
and O
will O
eventually O
support O
the O
C-130J O
Super B-PRODUCT
Hercules, I-PRODUCT
KC-130J B-TICKER
and O
legacy O
C-130 O
B–H O
variants. O

The O
CCI’s B-TICKER
AI B-TICKER
market O
study O
also O
notes O
that O
Indian O
startups O
are O
now O
integral O
to O
different O
layers O
of O
India’s O
AI B-TICKER
stack, O
from O
data O
services O
(like O
Extracto, B-ORG
ML B-ORG
Labs, I-ORG
and O
iMerit) B-ORG
to O
model O
development O
and O
generative O
AI B-TICKER
(such O
as O
Sarvam B-ORG
AI I-ORG
and O
Krutrim). B-ORG

Australia: B-GPE
Broad-based O
gains, O
but O
not O
universal O
Since O
the O
Comprehensive B-PRODUCT
Economic I-PRODUCT
Cooperation I-PRODUCT
and I-PRODUCT
Trade I-PRODUCT
Agreement I-PRODUCT
(ECTA) B-TICKER
came O
into O
force, O
India B-GPE
has O
strengthened O
its O
export O
footprint O
across O
a O
wide O
swathe O
of O
the O
Australian B-GPE
market. I-GPE

“Yes, O
there O
will O
be O
speculators O
in O
the O
market, O
but O
speculators O
are O
going O
to O
come O
into O
the O
market O
with O
an O
apprehension O
that O
they’re O
going O
to O
get O
hurt O
very O
badly O
because O
they O
don't O
know O
how O
to O
predict O
the O
RBI,” O
Mahalingam O
said, O
without O
going O
into O
any O
details O
of O
how O
the O
central O
bank O
conducts O
interventions. O

Procurement O
of O
Embraer-based O
Airborne O
Early O
Warning O
System, O
NETRA B-TICKER
AEW B-TICKER
integration O
are O
on O
agenda, O
the O
report O
added. O

The O
increase O
had O
to O
come O
on O
the O
back O
of O
the O
implementation O
of O
the O
FDTL B-TICKER
norms. O

Affordability O
business’ O
scale-up O
is O
leading O
to O
higher O
working O
capital O
investments, O
which O
resulted O
in O
Rs(2.15)bn O
FCF B-TICKER
for O
H1FY26. B-DATE

Spot O
silver B-INSTRUMENT
prices O
held O
strong O
at O
$58.46 B-MONEY
an O
ounce O
on O
December B-DATE
4, I-DATE
as O
of O
6:54 O
a.m O
(IST) B-TICKER
amid O
tight O
supply O
and O
hopes O
for O
additional O
rate O
cuts O
by O
the O
U.S B-ORG
Federal I-ORG
Reserve I-ORG
next O
week. O

Looser O
monetary O
policy O
is O
a O
tailwind O
for O
gold B-INSTRUMENT
and O
silver, B-INSTRUMENT
which O
don’t O
pay O
interest. O

The O
rise O
in O
defence B-INSTRUMENT
shares I-INSTRUMENT
today O
also O
comes O
on O
the O
back O
of O
US B-TICKER
ordering O
increased O
economic O
pressure O
on O
Venezuelan O
oil O
shipments O
and O
carrying O
out O
airstrikes O
against O
Islamic O
State O
militants O
in O
northwest O
Nigeria B-GPE
at O
the O
request O
of O
Nigeria's B-GPE
government. O

This O
came O
after O
the O
stock O
hit O
a O
fresh O
52-week O
high O
of O
Rs B-MONEY
656.35 I-MONEY
earlier O
during O
the O
day. O

However, O
as O
we O
were O
expecting, O
the O
MPC B-TICKER
has O
drawn O
comfort O
from O
the O
extremely O
low O
inflation O
prints O
and O
chosen O
to O
support O
the O
economy, O
while O
also O
announcing O
measures O
to O
improve O
durable O
liquidity. O

Subsequently, O
the O
watchdog O
held O
a O
review O
meeting O
with O
IndiGo, B-ORG
wherein O
the O
airline O
acknowledged O
that O
it O
had O
failed O
to O
anticipate O
the O
actual O
crew O
requirement O
under O
the O
revised O
norms O
and O
that O
significant O
planning O
and O
assessment O
gaps O
existed O
in O
implementing O
Phase-II O
of O
FDTL B-TICKER
CAR B-TICKER
2024, O
as O
per O
the O
order. O

UBS B-TICKER
kept O
its O
'Buy' O
call O
on O
the O
shares O
of O
IndiGo, O
but O
reduced O
its O
target O
price O
for O
the O
stock O
to O
Rs B-MONEY
6,350 I-MONEY
per O
share. O

Close O
to O
10 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
of O
our O
book O
today O
is O
home O
loans. O

The O
new O
framework O
focused O
on O
fair O
wages, O
smoother O
industrial O
relations, O
expanded O
social O
security O
coverage O
and O
improved O
workplace O
safety. O

crude O
oil O
output O
rose O
44,000 O
barrels O
per O
day O
in O
September B-DATE
to O
a O
record O
13.84 O
million O
bpd, O
according O
to O
the O
EIA B-TICKER
data. O

In O
the O
aftermath O
of O
the O
Pahalgam O
attack, O
which O
took O
place O
in O
April O
2025, O
the O
civil B-ORG
aviation I-ORG
ministry I-ORG
capped O
fares O
on O
flights O
out O
of O
Srinagar B-GPE
to O
ensure O
affordability. O

While O
the O
US-China B-TICKER
trade O
war O
had O
really O
escalated O
with O
the O
US B-TICKER
imposing O
a O
145% B-PERCENT
tariff O
on O
Chinese O
products O
and O
China O
reciprocating O
with O
125%, B-PERCENT
the O
last O
few O
months O
have O
seen O
a O
temporary O
truce O
with O
much O
lower O
tariffs O
on O
each O
other, O
some O
relaxation O
of O
China’s O
rare O
earth O
export O
controls O
and O
China O
promising O
to O
buy O
American O
soybeans. O

While O
it O
remains O
a O
dominant O
player O
in O
the O
entry O
segment, O
HMCL B-TICKER
targets O
to O
recover O
lost O
share O
in O
the O
125cc O
segment O
post O
recent O
variant O
launches O
of O
Glamour B-PRODUCT
and O
Xtreme125R, B-PRODUCT
which O
have O
been O
well O
received O
in O
the O
market. O

Domestically, O
demand O
continues O
to O
be O
driven O
by O
power O
T&D, O
renewables B-PRODUCT
and O
railways, O
while O
exports O
are O
supported O
by O
the O
US, B-TICKER
Asia, B-GPE
the O
Middle B-PERSON
East I-PERSON
and O
Africa. B-GPE

In O
emerging O
economies, O
the O
implications O
are O
even O
more O
profound, O
and O
the O
new O
entrants O
are O
undoubtedly O
benefitting O
from O
bespoke O
marketing O
strategies. O

The O
RBI O
has O
historically O
been O
opposed O
to O
providing O
liquidity O
facility O
to O
NBFCs, B-ORG
Mutual B-INSTRUMENT
Funds I-INSTRUMENT
and O
other O
entities O
in O
the O
money O
market. O

Turnover O
has O
picked O
up, O
signalling O
institutional O
interest O
returning O
after O
a O
weak O
November," O
the O
analyst O
said. O

In O
the O
FY26 B-DATE
Union B-EVENT
Budget, I-EVENT
Finance O
Minister O
Nirmala B-PERSON
Sitharaman I-PERSON
repositioned O
the O
debt-to-GDP B-METRIC
ratio I-METRIC
as O
the O
government's B-ORG
main O
fiscal O
anchor, O
replacing O
the O
long-standing O
practice O
of O
treating O
the O
fiscal O
deficit O
as O
the O
primary O
operational O
target. O

The O
index O
has O
now O
gained O
around O
5 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
in O
eight O
sessions O
of O
gains O
so O
far. O

India’s O
challenge O
is O
to O
guide O
this O
transition O
to O
strengthen O
resilience. O

Your O
age O
is O
83, O
will O
you O
ever O
stop O
or O
not? O

Jyoti O
CNC B-TICKER
Automation: O
Approaching O
a O
potential O
inflection O
point O
What O
else O
are O
we O
reading? O

Currently, O
around O
four O
mutual O
funds O
have O
launched O
SIF B-TICKER
products, O
including O
Edelweiss B-ORG
Mutual I-ORG
Fund, I-ORG
SBI B-TICKER
Mutual I-ORG
Fund, I-ORG
ITI B-ORG
AMC I-ORG
and O
Quant B-ORG
AMC, I-ORG
among O
others. O

About O
83% B-PERCENT
of O
NGOs B-ORG
find O
it O
hard O
to O
get O
flexible O
funding O
for O
support O
functions O
outside O
core O
programs, O
though O
68% B-PERCENT
of O
funders O
say O
their O
policies O
allow O
it. O

In O
fact, O
the O
implementation O
of O
the O
FDTL B-TICKER
norms O
from O
November O
1 O
emerged O
as O
the O
biggest O
reason O
for O
the O
flight O
cancellations O
that O
month. O

The O
stock O
is O
trading O
at O
a O
P/E B-METRIC
of O
56.1x/45.5x O
on O
FY27/28E. B-DATE

At O
this O
stage, O
there O
is O
simply O
no O
appetite O
for O
a O
3 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
sale, O
which O
would O
be O
nearly O
Rs B-MONEY
24,000 I-MONEY
crore,” I-MONEY
the O
source O
said, O
adding O
that O
the O
sale O
is O
being O
aligned O
with O
broader O
market O
conditions. O

The O
25 O
basis O
points O
rate O
cut O
comes O
in O
the O
backdrop O
of O
growth-inflation O
balance. O

Regulatory O
pressure O
intensified O
as O
the O
Directorate B-PERSON
General I-PERSON
of O
Civil B-PERSON
Aviation I-PERSON
(DGCA) B-TICKER
granted O
a O
one-time O
24-hour O
extension O
to O
CEO O
Pieter B-PERSON
Elbers I-PERSON
to O
respond O
to O
a O
show-cause O
notice O
issued O
on O
December O
6, O
after O
IndiGo B-ORG
officials O
sought O
more O
time O
citing O
operational O
constraints. O

RPA B-TICKER
facts O
that O
you O
should O
know O
Choosing O
the O
right O
solution O
is O
of O
utmost O
importance O
for O
improved O
efficiency O
If O
appropriately O
implemented, O
RPA B-TICKER
solutions O
can O
genuinely O
transform O
the O
BFSI B-TICKER
sector O
through O
fierce O
competition, O
workflow O
disconnects, O
and O
error-prone O
reporting. O

Tata B-ORG
Advanced I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
CEO O
and O
MD O
Sukaran B-PERSON
Singh I-PERSON
said O
the O
facility O
reflects O
India’s O
rising O
capability O
and O
ambition O
in O
defence O
manufacturing. O

Its O
price O
is O
0.32 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
down O
from O
their O
previous O
close. O

Tyre O
maker O
Ceat B-ORG
is O
developing O
tyres B-PRODUCT
for O
various O
global O
markets O
as O
it O
aims O
to O
expand O
its O
exports O
to O
regions O
like O
Europe B-GPE
and O
US B-TICKER
with O
plans O
to O
establish O
itself O
as O
a O
global O
brand, O
according O
to O
RPG B-TICKER
Group O
Vice O
Chairman O
Anant B-PERSON
Goenka. I-PERSON

If O
companies O
across O
insurance, O
mutual O
funds, O
and O
lending O
can O
pool O
data O
at O
a O
common O
source, O
it O
may O
be O
helpful O
to O
cull O
out O
bad O
agents/fraudsters O
in O
the O
payments O
system. O

They O
are O
now O
optimistic O
about O
embracing O
this O
investment O
avenue O
under O
the O
gloomy O
economic O
conditions. O

A O
daily O
close O
above O
Rs B-MONEY
1,880 I-MONEY
can O
confirm O
a O
breakout O
of O
the O
said O
pattern, O
which O
can O
push O
prices O
higher O
towards O
Rs B-MONEY
1,955, I-MONEY
followed O
by O
Rs B-MONEY
2,030, I-MONEY
with O
key O
support O
at O
Rs B-MONEY
1,805. I-MONEY

I O
think O
customer O
support O
is O
an O
obvious O
one O
where O
it O
lends O
itself O
very O
well. O

“This O
rise O
is O
being O
fueled O
by O
prolonged O
geopolitical O
tensions O
(Venezuela B-EVENT
Blockade I-EVENT
and O
Caribbean B-EVENT
Naval I-EVENT
Tension), I-EVENT
aggressive O
central-bank O
buying, O
supply O
interruptions O
in O
Silver, O
and O
a O
global B-ORG
investing I-ORG
community I-ORG
more O
concerned O
about O
economic O
and O
political O
unpredictability,” O
the O
report O
stated. O

Drawing O
a O
comparison O
with O
earlier O
tax O
reforms, O
Sitharaman O
recalled O
how O
the O
income O
tax O
system O
once O
struggled O
with O
administrative O
complexities O
even O
when O
rates O
themselves O
were O
not O
the O
core O
issue. O

2) O
Heavy O
selling O
in O
small B-INSTRUMENT
and I-INSTRUMENT
midcap I-INSTRUMENT
shares: I-INSTRUMENT
The O
small- O
and O
mid-cap O
shares O
came O
under O
sharp O
selling O
pressure O
on O
Monday O
as O
investors O
booked O
profits, O
dragging O
several O
stocks O
down. O

Other O
precious O
metals O
also O
surged. O

PC B-ORG
Jeweller I-ORG
said O
the O
tie-up O
will O
offer O
support O
in O
branding, O
design, O
modern O
retail O
practices, O
digital O
skills O
and O
market O
linkages. O

Spot O
silver O
for O
immediate O
delivery O
advanced O
for O
a O
fifth O
session, O
climbing O
as O
much O
as O
4.6% B-PERCENT
to O
cross O
$75 B-MONEY
an O
ounce. O

oil O
production O
rose O
to O
record O
highs O
in O
September, O
data O
from O
the O
Energy B-ORG
Information I-ORG
Administration I-ORG
showed O
on O
Friday, O
deepening O
concerns O
that O
the O
market O
is O
heading O
towards O
a O
surplus. O

Is O
it O
because O
you O
focus O
on O
big-ticket O
loans, O
unlike O
a O
lot O
of O
fintechs, O
which O
mostly O
play O
in O
the O
small-ticket O
category, O
so O
it O
doesn't O
make O
sense O
for O
them O
to O
acquire O
at O
a O
very O
high O
cost? O

IndiGo B-ORG
on O
Sunday O
operated O
1,650 O
flights O
out O
of O
its O
usual O
2,300 O
daily O
domestic O
and O
international O
services, O
while O
around O
650 O
remained O
cancelled O
as O
the O
airline O
continued O
efforts O
to O
restore O
normalcy O
following O
five O
days O
of O
major O
disruptions, O
the O
carrier O
said. O

“Consumer O
prices O
in O
the O
United B-GPE
States I-GPE
increased O
2.7% B-PERCENT
year O
on O
year O
in O
November, O
falling O
short O
of O
the O
3.1 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
expected. O

The O
platforms’ O
position O
and O
their O
silence O
Platform O
companies O
insist O
their O
models O
offer O
flexibility O
and O
opportunity. O

Shyam B-ORG
Dhani I-ORG
Industries I-ORG
IPO O
shares O
attracted O
a O
massive O
100 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
premium O
in O
the O
grey O
market, O
while O
Dachepalli B-PERSON
Publishers, I-PERSON
and O
EPW B-TICKER
India O
shares O
saw O
moderate O
premium, O
but O
Gujarat B-GPE
Kidney O
& O
Super B-PERSON
Speciality, I-PERSON
and O
Sundrex B-ORG
Oil I-ORG
Company I-ORG
IPO O
shares O
have O
not O
attracted O
any O
premium, O
the O
market O
observers O
said. O

This O
week, O
a O
US B-TICKER
federal O
judge O
rejected O
a O
challenge O
by O
the O
US B-TICKER
Chamber O
of O
Commerce O
to O
President B-PERSON
Donald I-PERSON
Trump’s I-PERSON
proposed O
$100,000 B-MONEY
fee O
on O
new O
H-1B O
visas, O
ruling O
that O
it O
falls O
within O
the O
president’s O
broad O
authority O
to O
regulate O
immigration. O

A O
country O
that O
normalises O
round-the-clock O
tracking O
of O
everyone O
to O
fight O
cybercrime O
will O
unleash O
so O
much O
distrust O
among O
people O
that O
it O
will O
destroy O
the O
already O
fragile O
societal O
trust O
within O
communities. O

CRISIL O
notes O
households O
are O
shifting O
from O
traditional O
deposits O
to O
mutual O
funds, O
equities, O
pensions, O
and O
insurance. O

Comex B-PERSON
Gold I-PERSON
held O
near O
$4,200 B-MONEY
in O
a O
tight O
intraday O
range O
between O
$4,228 B-MONEY
and O
$4,200," B-MONEY
said O
Jateen B-PERSON
Trivedi, I-PERSON
VP B-TICKER
Research B-PERSON
Analyst I-PERSON
- O
Commodity O
and O
Currency, O
LKP B-TICKER
Securities. O

The O
ATGMs B-PRODUCT
(Anti-Tank B-PRODUCT
Guided I-PRODUCT
Missiles) I-PRODUCT
is O
to O
be O
executed O
in O
a O
span O
of O
42 O
months O
and O
Surface-to-Air B-PRODUCT
Missiles I-PRODUCT
(SAMs) B-PRODUCT
is O
to O
be O
executed O
in O
a O
span O
of O
12 O
months. O

Mahindra B-INSTRUMENT
& I-INSTRUMENT
Mahindra I-INSTRUMENT
Financial I-INSTRUMENT
Services, I-INSTRUMENT
Bharat B-INSTRUMENT
Dynamics, I-INSTRUMENT
Housing B-INSTRUMENT
& I-INSTRUMENT
Urban I-INSTRUMENT
Development I-INSTRUMENT
Corporation I-INSTRUMENT
and O
Prestige B-INSTRUMENT
Estates I-INSTRUMENT
Projects I-INSTRUMENT
were O
also O
down O
as O
much O
as O
5 B-PERCENT
percent. I-PERCENT

Zeta B-ORG
provides O
a O
full-stack O
cloud O
native O
banking O
platform O
for O
banks O
and O
fintechs. O

The O
government B-ORG
currently O
holds O
a O
96.5 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
stake O
in O
LIC. B-TICKER

If O
India O
needs O
to O
grow O
at O
8-9% B-PERCENT
and O
become O
Viksit O
Bharat O
by O
2047, O
who O
but O
Indian O
businesses O
will O
bring O
the O
capital, O
goes O
the O
argument. O

Base O
metals O
on O
the O
LME B-TICKER
ended O
the O
week O
on O
strong O
footing, O
with O
copper O
leading O
the O
pack O
after O
rising O
more O
than O
3 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
to O
trade O
near O
$11,180 B-MONEY
a O
ton. O

Siddharth B-PERSON
Maurya, I-PERSON
Founder O
& O
Managing O
Director O
at O
Vibhavangal B-ORG
Anukulakara, I-ORG
noted O
"The​‍​‌‍​‍‌​‍​‌‍​‍‌ O
fall O
is O
mainly O
due O
to O
a O
nervous O
worldwide O
atmosphere. O

Expanding O
operations O
into O
more O
cities O
are O
also O
likely O
to O
be O
part O
of O
the O
plan. O

"With O
markets O
pricing O
in O
a O
gradual O
easing O
cycle O
in O
the O
US, B-TICKER
the O
dollar O
index O
has O
eased O
from O
recent O
highs, O
supporting O
dollar-denominated O
commodities. O

I O
think O
the O
regulator O
is O
trying O
to O
get O
a O
grip O
on O
how O
to O
regulate O
this O
space. O

Challenges O
and O
road O
ahead O
As O
2025 O
ends, O
agriculture O
faces O
persistent O
challenges, O
including O
fragmented O
landholdings, O
climate O
change O
risks, O
35-40 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent I-PERCENT
post-harvest O
losses O
for O
perishables, O
and O
tenant O
farmers' O
exclusion O
from O
schemes. O

I O
think O
we O
have O
to O
wait O
for O
the O
regulator O
to O
come O
and O
say, O
"Yes, O
we O
are O
open O
to O
it. O

Some O
of O
the O
topics O
of O
discussion O
were O
industry-wide. O

Such O
positions O
mean O
the O
RBI O
has O
pledged O
to O
sell O
dollars O
in O
the O
future O
and O
would O
need O
to O
source O
them O
for O
delivery O
when O
they O
mature. O

Organically O
also, O
some O
costs O
for O
COFORGE O
witnessed O
an O
uptick O
in O
recent O
quarters, O
which O
may O
strain O
its O
margins, O
going O
ahead. O

Speaking O
with O
CNBC B-TICKER
TV18 B-ORG
on O
the O
occasion O
of O
its O
26th O
anniversary, O
Kalra O
differentiated O
between O
the O
underlying O
technology's O
long-term O
impact O
and O
market B-METRIC
valuations, I-METRIC
providing O
a O
detailed O
outlook O
on O
how O
AI B-TICKER
will O
reshape O
various O
sectors O
and O
drive O
growth O
for O
IT B-TICKER
services O
firms. O

This O
sharp O
reversal O
in O
retail O
flows O
has O
added O
to O
the O
government’s O
caution O
in O
timing O
the O
LIC B-TICKER
OFS. B-TICKER

Follow O
all O
IPO O
news O
here. O

Banks O
also O
perform O
semi O
fiscal O
roles O
like O
lending O
mandatorily O
to O
the O
priority O
sector O
and O
providing O
basic O
banking O
facilities O
free O
of O
cost. O

The O
way O
Flipkart B-ORG
scaled O
in O
10 O
years, O
was O
unimaginable. O

They O
point O
to O
accident O
insurance O
during O
active O
deliveries, O
incentive O
payouts, O
and O
the O
ability O
for O
workers O
to O
choose O
when O
to O
log O
in. O

Speaking O
at O
the O
HT B-EVENT
Leadership I-EVENT
Summit, I-EVENT
she O
said O
the O
customs O
framework O
needs O
significant O
simplification O
and O
greater O
clarity. O

Therefore, O
5G O
will O
enable O
higher O
productivity O
with O
connected O
devices O
and O
will O
also O
champion O
superior, O
customised O
and O
digital O
financial O
experience O
in O
the O
coming O
years. O

Together, O
these O
cases O
highlight O
a O
core O
principle: O
competition O
law O
is O
guided O
by O
consumer O
benefit, O
and O
integration O
that O
expands O
functionality O
without O
limiting O
choice O
meets O
that O
test. O

With O
IndiGo B-ORG
controlling O
65 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
of O
the O
country’s O
domestic O
aviation O
market, O
the O
widespread O
disruption O
caused O
by O
its O
cancellation O
of O
3,500 O
flights O
since O
the O
start O
of O
December, O
upset O
the O
schedules O
of O
other O
airlines, O
leaving O
travellers O
stranded O
across O
major O
airports. O

Using O
software O
robots, O
which O
mimic O
UI-based B-TICKER
human O
actions O
to O
perform O
everyday O
tasks, O
one O
can O
keep O
the O
underlying O
IT B-TICKER
infrastructure O
intact. O

The O
official O
told O
PTI B-TICKER
that O
the O
immediate O
priority O
is O
to O
restore O
normal O
flight O
operations, O
and O
the O
airline O
has O
been O
instructed O
to O
ensure O
prompt O
refund O
of O
tickets O
to O
affected O
passengers. O

The O
impact O
would O
not O
stop O
with O
big O
technological O
companies O
- O
it’s O
not O
just O
the O
big O
players O
at O
stake. O

With O
direct O
access O
to O
actionable O
insights, O
they O
can O
build O
a O
loan O
distribution O
model O
that O
increases O
trust, O
reduces O
risk O
and O
in O
turn, O
the O
acquisition O
costs. O

By O
consolidating O
29 O
central O
labour O
laws O
into O
four O
streamlined O
codes, O
the O
reforms O
aimed O
to O
provide O
regulatory O
clarity O
for O
employers O
while O
strengthening O
protections O
for O
workers. O

He O
highlighted O
that O
over O
the O
last O
decade, O
Biocon's O
profitability O
growth O
has O
been O
modest, O
at O
around O
9-10%, B-PERCENT
while O
its O
return B-METRIC
on I-METRIC
equity I-METRIC
(ROE) B-TICKER
has O
remained O
in O
the O
mid-single O
digits. O

Precious B-PRODUCT
metals, I-PRODUCT
however, O
are O
projected O
to O
rise O
by O
around O
5 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent I-PERCENT
next O
year, O
building O
on O
a O
strong O
investment-led O
gain O
of O
over O
40 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent I-PERCENT
in O
2025, O
according O
to O
a O
report O
by O
financial O
services O
firm O
Prabhudas B-ORG
Lilladher. I-ORG

On O
the O
Multi B-ORG
Commodity I-ORG
Exchange I-ORG
(MCX), B-TICKER
silver B-INSTRUMENT
futures I-INSTRUMENT
for O
March B-DATE
2026 I-DATE
delivery O
tumbled O
by O
Rs B-MONEY
3,253, I-MONEY
or O
1.79 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent, I-PERCENT
to O
Rs B-MONEY
1,78,777 I-MONEY
per O
kilogram O
in O
14,678 O
lots. O

With O
AI, B-TICKER
there O
is O
no O
reason O
why O
you O
cannot O
unearth O
Interconnected O
lending,” O
he O
told O
me. O

Silver B-INSTRUMENT
has O
also O
been O
supported O
by O
a O
wave O
of O
speculative O
money O
betting O
on O
supply O
tightness. O

After O
all, O
we O
did O
not O
rebel O
against O
the O
British B-PERSON
Raj I-PERSON
to O
escape O
becoming O
Macaulay-Putras O
to O
gain O
our O
freedom O
only O
to O
become O
Orwell-Putras O
75 O
years O
later. O

The O
current O
level O
may O
see O
some O
selective O
buying, O
but O
overall O
momentum O
stays O
restricted. O

One O
such O
project O
is O
the O
upcoming O
Taj O
Bandstand O
hotel O
in O
Mumbai, O
for O
which O
the O
company O
recently O
completed O
a O
₹101-crore B-MONEY
rights O
issue. O

Equally O
essential O
is O
judicially-monitored O
access O
to O
sensitive O
data—oversight O
that O
ensures O
the O
state’s O
powers O
are O
targeted, O
proportionate O
and O
accountable. O

The O
airport O
authority O
urged O
travellers O
to O
verify O
their O
flight O
status O
before O
leaving O
for O
the O
terminal, O
noting O
that O
schedules O
remain O
unstable O
as O
the O
airline O
works O
to O
restore O
normal O
operations. O

On O
the O
downside, O
Rs B-MONEY
8,780 I-MONEY
is O
the O
nearest O
support O
to O
watch O
out O
for. O

The O
decision O
over O
whether O
and O
how O
to O
intervene O
takes O
place O
every O
morning O
before O
markets O
open O
in O
the O
RBI’s O
headquarters O
in O
south O
Mumbai, O
where O
the O
Financial B-ORG
Markets I-ORG
Committee I-ORG
comprising O
officials O
from O
different O
departments O
meets O
to O
discuss O
various O
pressures O
on O
the O
exchange O
rate. O

It O
is O
about O
getting O
better--deeper O
skills, O
higher O
responsibility, O
stronger O
pay. O

PhonePe, B-ORG
Flipkart, B-ORG
Zepto, B-ORG
boAt, B-ORG
Shiprocket, B-ORG
Infra.Market, B-ORG
OfBusiness B-ORG
and O
Shadowfax B-ORG
are O
among O
the O
firms O
looking O
to O
tap O
the O
public O
markets O
— O
a O
line-up O
that O
suggests O
demand O
is O
broad-based O
rather O
than O
sector-specific. O

Strategy: O
Buy B-PERSON
Target: I-PERSON
Rs B-MONEY
9,250, I-MONEY
Rs B-MONEY
9,400, I-MONEY
Rs B-MONEY
9,650 I-MONEY
Stop-Loss: O
Rs B-MONEY
8,780 I-MONEY
The O
banking O
sector O
has O
been O
one O
of O
the O
standout O
performers O
in O
recent O
times, O
with O
public-sector O
banks O
taking O
the O
lead. O

Sanjiv B-PERSON
Bajaj I-PERSON
wouldn’t O
buy O
that O
argument. O

Recent O
readings O
above O
80 O
have O
consistently O
triggered O
market O
pullbacks, O
and O
this O
week O
proved O
no O
exception. O

He O
was O
speaking O
during O
an O
exclusive O
interaction O
with O
Moneycontrol B-ORG
at O
the O
AMC’s B-ORG
bumper O
IPO B-EVENT
launch. I-EVENT

Indeed, O
even O
in O
the O
past, O
the O
RBI O
has O
underestimated O
or O
overestimated O
inflation O
consistently O
and O
has O
done O
the O
same O
on O
growth. O

• O
Building O
a O
mobile O
payment O
platform O
– O
Financial O
and O
non-financial O
institutions O
can O
leverage O
digital O
wallets O
and O
mobile O
payments O
to O
facilitate O
new O
ways O
to O
pay O
and O
get O
paid. O

Goldman B-ORG
Sachs I-ORG
Group I-ORG
Inc. O

“This O
week, O
US B-TICKER
data, O
including O
new O
home O
sales, O
the O
Core O
PCE B-METRIC
price I-METRIC
index, I-METRIC
and O
weekly O
jobless O
claim O
will O
remain O
crucial O
triggers O
for O
further O
price O
direction," O
said O
Jateen B-PERSON
Trivedi, I-PERSON
VP O
Research O
Analyst O
- O
Commodity O
and O
Currency, O
LKP B-ORG
Securities. I-ORG

FDTL B-TICKER
is O
designed O
to O
reduce O
fatigue O
and O
improve O
safety. O

The O
December B-DATE
31 I-DATE
strike O
is O
expected O
to O
be O
broader O
and O
more O
disruptive. O

Platinum B-INSTRUMENT
has O
more O
than O
doubled. O

The O
status O
will O
also O
be O
available O
on O
the O
BSE B-ORG
and O
NSE B-ORG
websites. O

Our O
median O
is O
between O
Rs B-MONEY
50,000 I-MONEY
to O
Rs B-MONEY
1 I-MONEY
lakh. I-MONEY

Motilal B-ORG
Oswal's I-ORG
research O
report O
on O
Apollo B-ORG
Tyres I-ORG
We O
met O
Apollo B-ORG
Tyres’ I-ORG
(APTY) B-TICKER
management O
to O
understand O
the O
outlook O
for O
its O
key O
segments. O

Cholamandalam B-PERSON
Inv I-PERSON
and I-PERSON
Fin I-PERSON
- O
24122025 O
- O
moti O

Too O
little O
and O
one-way O
bets O
can O
escalate, O
deepening O
the O
slump. O

However, O
he O
cautioned O
against O
expecting O
immediate O
scale. O

Speaking O
about O
the O
SIF B-TICKER
category, O
Shah O
said O
SEBI B-ORG
“has O
thought O
through O
the O
SIF B-TICKER
category O
very O
well,” O
adding O
that O
the O
segment O
holds O
significant O
long-term O
promise. O

"With O
this O
merger O
coming O
into O
play, O
it's O
not O
that O
it's O
value O
accretive O
or O
EPS B-TICKER
accretive, O
I O
think O
it's O
EPS B-TICKER
dilutive," O
he O
stated. O

JM B-TICKER
Financial O
said O
that O
the O
valuation O
looks O
rich O
given O
Encora’s O
7 O
– O
10 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
growth O
profile, O
CNBC-TV18 B-TICKER
reported. O

Outside O
of O
their O
home O
base O
in O
US, B-TICKER
India B-GPE
is O
the O
second O
largest O
employee O
base O
for O
the O
card O
network O
giant. O

Rupee O
weakness O
continues O
to O
give O
MCX B-TICKER
Gold O
an O
additional O
lift, O
but O
the O
current O
zone O
is O
overbought O
and O
a O
retracement O
toward O
the O
Rs B-MONEY
1,27,000 I-MONEY
support O
cannot O
be O
ruled O
out," O
said O
Trivedi. O

Energy B-ORG
Information I-ORG
Administration I-ORG
will O
release O
official O
government O
stockpile O
data O
later O
on O
Wednesday. O

Sector O
executives O
say O
that O
if O
the O
regulator O
grants O
any O
concessions, O
it O
will O
have O
to O
ensure O
a O
level O
playing O
field. O

# O
Tax O
and O
Regulatory O
Reforms: O
The O
government’s B-ORG
move O
to O
simplify O
GST O
rates O
from O
five O
to O
three O
slabs O
marks O
a O
significant O
reform. O

A O
softer O
price O
regime O
has O
been O
one O
of O
the O
biggest O
wins O
for O
the O
RBI's O
inflation O
targeting O
framework. O

Hence, O
this O
issue O
needs O
to O
be O
suitably O
addressed. O

Our O
goal O
is O
to O
become O
a O
global O
brand. O

“Whereas O
such O
large-scale O
operational O
failures O
indicate O
significant O
lapses O
in O
planning, O
oversight, O
and O
resource O
management, O
and O
is O
prima O
facie O
non-compliance O
on O
the O
part O
of O
the O
airline…” O
the O
notice O
stated, O
placing O
responsibility O
directly O
on O
the O
CEO. O

The O
industry O
can O
run O
in O
an O
efficient O
way O
to O
manage O
operation O
challenges, O
and O
compliances O
to O
secure O
margins O
along O
with O
resource O
allocations O
to O
work O
towards O
investment O
and O
effective O
customer O
management O
The O
author O
is O
Country O
Director O
- O
India O
at O
Micro B-ORG
Focus, I-ORG
a O
British O
multinational O
pureplay O
software O
company, O
with O
a O
revenue O
of O
over O
USD B-MONEY
4 I-MONEY
billion. I-MONEY

But O
if O
you O
see O
the O
trend O
from O
the O
last O
couple O
of O
years, O
there O
was O
this O
credit O
card O
model O
that O
was O
looked O
at. O

The O
morning O
session O
saw O
the O
cryptocurrency O
fall O
as O
low O
as O
$84,682 B-MONEY
and O
peaked O
just O
above O
$87,193. B-MONEY

The O
insurance O
businesses O
will O
integrate O
more O
closely O
with O
the O
group’s O
health O
and O
digital O
platforms, O
enabling O
bundled O
offerings O
that O
combine O
health O
services O
with O
insurance, O
hybrid O
protection-health O
products, O
SME-focused B-TICKER
commercial O
insurance O
solutions, O
and O
future-ready O
pension-linked O
or O
annuity O
products O
once O
full O
consolidation O
is O
complete. O

I O
mean, O
I O
am O
saying O
myself, O
as O
an O
operator O
in O
the O
startup O
space, O
and O
as O
a O
small-time O
investor, O
I O
kind O
of O
took O
governance O
mostly O
for O
granted—that O
most O
of O
the O
founders O
are O
from O
good O
backgrounds. O

For O
affected O
households, O
timely O
financial O
support O
improves O
recovery O
and O
stability. O

Martin B-PERSON
Wolf I-PERSON
of O
the O
Financial B-ORG
Times I-ORG
had O
correctly O
predicted O
that O
Trump’s B-PERSON
first O
term O
tariffs O
would O
look O
like O
“relatively O
modest O
starter O
protectionism” O
in O
comparison O
with O
his O
second O
term O
trade O
policy. O

What O
should O
matter O
to O
investors O
is O
the O
fate O
of O
corporate O
earnings O
growth. O

“When O
the O
markets O
corrected, O
the O
SIPs O
didn’t O
stop. O

The O
RBI’s O
ban O
order O
in O
2018 O
had O
already O
pushed O
the O
country’s O
crypto O
community O
to O
step O
back O
and O
either O
shut O
shop O
or O
move O
their O
operations O
overseas. O

Sometimes O
the O
change O
favours O
investors O
— O
sometimes O
it O
compresses O
returns. O

If O
you O
want O
safety O
over O
returns O
— O
stick O
to O
high-quality B-PRODUCT
liquid, I-PRODUCT
ultra-short B-PRODUCT
or I-PRODUCT
money-market I-PRODUCT
funds. I-PRODUCT

TDS B-TICKER
could O
now O
be O
used O
to O
establish O
transaction O
trail, O
as O
a O
backstop, O
only O
in O
cases O
where O
transaction O
trail O
is O
not O
available O
from O
these O
sources. O

Paytm O
absent O
Yet O
for O
the O
next O
60 O
minutes, O
not O
a O
single O
founder O
brought O
up O
the O
elephant O
in O
the O
room- O
Paytm. O

In O
the O
SIP B-TICKER
scenario, O
the O
uninvested O
money O
often O
sits O
in O
a O
savings B-INSTRUMENT
account I-INSTRUMENT
earning O
barely O
3 B-PERCENT
per I-PERCENT
cent. I-PERCENT

Mass O
surveillance O
may O
begin O
as O
an O
anti-fraud O
tool, O
but O
it O
rarely O
stays O
that O
way. O

2) I-MONEY
Persistent O
FII B-TICKER
selling: O
Foreign B-PERSON
Institutional I-PERSON
Investors I-PERSON
(FIIs) O
sold O
equities O
worth O
Rs B-MONEY
317.56 I-MONEY
crore I-MONEY
on O
Friday, O
marking O
the O
fourth O
consecutive O
session O
of O
net O
outflows. O

There O
is O
no O
clarity O
yet O
on O
when O
this O
will O
happen. O

Agricultural O
and O
food O
products O
form O
a O
second O
pillar O
of O
India’s B-GPE
expansion O
opportunity. O

Indeed O
Bajaj O
Auto O
has O
now O
set O
up O
its O
own O
finance O
company O
to O
lend O
to O
buyers O
of O
Bajaj O
2-wheelers, O
since O
they O
find O
that O
Bajaj B-ORG
Finance I-ORG
doesn’t O
give O
their O
customers O
any O
preferential O
treatment. O

“In O
the O
revised O
excise O
framework… O
valuation O
issues O
may O
trigger O
litigation, O
particularly O
on O
whether O
the O
‘duty O
price’ O
principle O
has O
been O
correctly O
applied,” O
Alay B-PERSON
Razvi, I-PERSON
Managing O
Partner, O
Accord B-ORG
Juris, I-ORG
told O
Moneycontrol. B-ORG

Championing O
access O
to O
the O
best O
and O
latest O
from O
fashion O
that O
resonates O
with O
India's O
diverse O
audience O
and O
meets O
their O
unique O
needs, O
the O
year O
saw O
the O
most O
sought-after O
fashion O
brands O
and O
lines O
being O
introduced O
to O
customers, O
including O
BCBG, O
North O
Face, O
Levi'sXAlia B-PERSON
Bhat, I-PERSON
Underneat, O
Satya B-PERSON
Paul, I-PERSON
GulaboXAbu-Sandeep, B-PERSON
CrocsXRashmika O
Mandana B-PERSON
and O
RI B-TICKER
by O
Ritu B-PERSON
Kumar, I-PERSON
among O
others. O

Why O
are O
gold O
prices O
rising? O

"The O
exemption O
is O
granted O
solely O
to O
facilitate O
operational O
stabilization O
and O
shall O
not O
be O
construed O
as O
dilution O
of O
safety O
requirements," O
DGCA B-TICKER
said O
in O
its O
directive. O

Platinum O
climbed O
4% B-PERCENT
and O
palladium O
rose O
4.4%. B-PERCENT

Among O
emerging O
businesses, O
Bajaj B-ORG
Finserv I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Ltd., O
following O
its O
integration O
with O
Vidal B-ORG
Healthcare, I-ORG
posted O
Rs B-MONEY
892 I-MONEY
crore I-MONEY
in O
consolidated O
revenue. O

No O
permanent O
deal O
has O
been O
reached O
yet, O
and O
trade O
tensions O
between O
the O
two O
countries O
are O
still O
strong. O

Tax O
rules O
evolve, O
and O
so O
do O
valuation O
norms. O

Robotic O
Process O
Automation O
(RPA) B-TICKER
is O
considered O
as O
the O
essential O
step O
towards O
automation. O

The O
shares O
of O
the O
IT B-TICKER
firm O
rose O
to O
Rs B-MONEY
1,711 I-MONEY
apiece O
in O
the O
early O
trading O
hours O
of O
Monday, O
snapping O
a O
three-session O
losing O
streak. O

INITIAL O
AIRLINE O
RESPONSE: O
IndiGo O
acknowledged O
widespread O
problems O
for O
the O
first O
time O
on O
December B-DATE
3, I-DATE
and O
attributed O
it O
to O
a O
multitude O
of O
factors O
– O
minor O
technology O
glitches, O
schedule O
changes O
linked O
to O
the O
winter O
season, O
adverse O
weather O
conditions, O
increased O
congestion O
in O
the O
aviation O
system O
and O
implementation O
of O
updated O
crew O
rostering O
rules O
(Flight B-METRIC
Duty I-METRIC
Time I-METRIC
Limitations).The I-METRIC
airline O
said O
all O
these O
factors O
worked O
together O
to O
have O
a O
”negative O
compounding O
impact O
on O
our O
operations O
in O
a O
way O
that O
was O
not O
feasible O
to O
be O
anticipated”.IndiGo O
also O
said O
it O
would O
provide O
refunds O
or O
alternate O
travel O
arrangements.It O
said O
the O
cancellations O
arose O
primarily O
from O
”misjudgment O
and O
planning O
gaps”. O

The O
index O
has O
now O
gained O
around O
5 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
in O
eight O
sessions O
of O
gains O
so O
far. O

Strategy: O
Buy O
Target: O
Rs B-MONEY
1,404, I-MONEY
Rs B-MONEY
1,420, I-MONEY
Rs B-MONEY
1,450 I-MONEY
Stop-Loss: O
Rs B-MONEY
1,335 I-MONEY
Consolidation O
is O
visible O
on O
the O
chart, O
yet O
M&M B-TICKER
maintains O
a O
bullish O
bias O
by O
trading O
above O
its O
10-, O
20-, O
and O
50-day O
moving O
averages. O

Kaynes B-INSTRUMENT
Technology I-INSTRUMENT
India I-INSTRUMENT
was O
the O
biggest O
loser O
in O
the O
Smallcap100 B-INSTRUMENT
pack. O

“These O
are O
grants O
meant O
for O
states, B-GPE
but O
they O
are O
released O
based O
on O
recommendations O
of O
concerned O
ministries,” O
the O
source O
said. O

There O
is O
a O
need O
for O
easing O
compliance O
burden, O
strengthening O
the O
dispute O
resolution O
framework O
and O
providing O
clarity O
on O
various O
issues O
where O
ambiguities O
and O
interpretational O
challenges O
could O
brew O
litigation O
in O
coming O
years. O

Today, O
enterprises O
provide O
a O
practical, O
non-invasive O
way O
to O
build, O
scale, O
and O
secure O
automated O
business O
processes O
across O
verticals. O

The O
MPC B-TICKER
also O
decided O
to O
continue O
with O
the O
neutral O
stance. O

The O
central O
bank O
slashed O
the O
federal O
funds O
rate O
by O
25 O
bps O
to O
3.5-3.75 B-PERCENT
percent I-PERCENT
range O
in O
the O
said O
meeting, O
after O
the O
25-bp O
reduction O
each O
in O
September O
and O
October. O

Private B-ORG
sector I-ORG
banks, I-ORG
NFBCs, B-ORG
peer-to-peer B-ORG
lending I-ORG
platforms I-ORG
are O
also O
bearing O
the O
brunt O
of O
loan O
defaults. O

The O
white O
metal’s O
recent O
advance O
has O
been O
buoyed O
by O
speculative O
inflows O
and O
lingering O
supply O
dislocations O
across O
major O
trading O
hubs O
following O
a O
historic O
short O
squeeze O
in O
October. O

During O
the O
post-policy O
press O
conference, O
the O
Governor O
reiterated O
the O
significance O
of O
maintaining O
benign O
inflation O
and O
ensuring O
effective O
monetary O
policy O
transmission. O

Digital O
gold O
vs O
other O
gold O
investments O
Digital O
gold O
is O
extremely O
convenient O
but O
lacks O
the O
regulation, O
transparent O
pricing, O
and O
liquidity O
of O
ETFs O
or O
mutual O
funds. O

“When O
the O
customer O
is O
selling, O
the O
fund O
is O
buying. O

For O
now, O
the O
revised O
national O
accounts O
will O
continue O
to O
rely O
on O
2019 O
survey O
weights, O
with O
officials O
noting O
that O
a O
further O
update O
could O
be O
done O
if O
post-pandemic O
shifts O
in O
household O
savings O
and O
investment O
behaviour O
turn O
out O
to O
be O
significant. O

IPO O
Action O
The O
activity O
at O
the O
IPO O
desk O
will O
be O
muted O
next O
week O
with O
only O
one O
IPO O
getting O
launched O
which O
is O
from O
the O
SME B-TICKER
segment. O

He O
added O
that O
underlying O
factors O
for O
the O
rally O
such O
as O
monetary O
policy O
easing, O
de-dollarisation, O
and O
global B-EVENT
trade I-EVENT
tensions I-EVENT
will O
continue O
to O
dominate O
in O
2026. O

The O
stock B-INSTRUMENT
had O
listed O
with O
a O
discount O
on O
stock B-GPE
markets I-GPE
on O
November O
10. O

